<wpjb>
    <jobs>
        <job>
            <id>2934225592</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Communications/DSP Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astraniscommunicationsdsp-engineer2019-05-08</job_slug>
            <job_description>Communications/DSP EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS
                CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to
                make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change
                that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring
                the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleWork with a small team of
                signal processing/communications engineers to develop and implement various radio functions (filtering,
                gain control, frequency tracking, digital upconversion/downconversion, linearization, timing and phase
                recovery, equalization, FEC, symbol mapping/demapping, framing, etc )Develop and maintain an end-to-end
                simulation of the entire radio system in Python Work closely with FPGA developers to implement, test and
                debug all signal processing modulesDesign spectrum diagnostics tool to support monitoring and debugging
                of the radio on orbitRequirementsBachelor of Science degree in electrical engineering or
                equivalentStrong fundamentals in "signals and systems" (basic transforms, aliasing, analysis in both
                continuous and discrete domains, interpolation, decimation, etc) Experience with digital communication
                theory, simulation, implementation and debugging (modulation, coding)Experience with testing and
                debugging radio hardware (signal generator, signal analyzer, network analyzer, oscilloscope)Strong RF
                fundamentals (amplifiers, antennas, analog filters, gain and delay variation, reflections, compression,
                etc)Strong software/firmware fundamentals (experience writing firmware for DSP/MCU/FPGA, scripting,
                developing simulations, etc)A passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced
                environment and hands-on design and developmentUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusMS or PhD in a signal
                processing field (digital communications, image processing, audio processing, ML/AI, etc)3 years
                experience working on software defined radios or modem ASICsExperience with PythonExperience with GNU
                RadioExperience with radio test planning, automation and executionExperience with multi-rate signal
                processing techniques (polyphase filter banks, resampling techniques)Experience with RTL development
                (and/or embedded C)Experience with fixed point implementation (managing precision, quantization noise,
                underflow, overflow, unit testing, etc)Experience with PA linearizationExperience with multi-antenna
                systems (beamforming, MIMO)Experience with DVB-S2/x, DVB-RCS2 standardsExperience with Satellite radio
                systems (ground segment and/or space segment)Apply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>124</job_country>
            <job_state>QC</job_state>
            <job_city>Gatineau</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-08</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-11</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
    </jobs>
</wpjb>
