<wpjb>
    <jobs>
        <job>
            <id>1999181366</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Communications/DSP Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astraniscommunicationsdsp-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Communications/DSP EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS
                CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to
                make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change
                that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring
                the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleWork with a small team of
                signal processing/communications engineers to develop and implement various radio functions (filtering,
                gain control, frequency tracking, digital upconversion/downconversion, linearization, timing and phase
                recovery, equalization, FEC, symbol mapping/demapping, framing, etc )Develop and maintain an end-to-end
                simulation of the entire radio system in Python Work closely with FPGA developers to implement, test and
                debug all signal processing modulesDesign spectrum diagnostics tool to support monitoring and debugging
                of the radio on orbitRequirementsBachelor of Science degree in electrical engineering or
                equivalentStrong fundamentals in "signals and systems" (basic transforms, aliasing, analysis in both
                continuous and discrete domains, interpolation, decimation, etc) Experience with digital communication
                theory, simulation, implementation and debugging (modulation, coding)Experience with testing and
                debugging radio hardware (signal generator, signal analyzer, network analyzer, oscilloscope)Strong RF
                fundamentals (amplifiers, antennas, analog filters, gain and delay variation, reflections, compression,
                etc)Strong software/firmware fundamentals (experience writing firmware for DSP/MCU/FPGA, scripting,
                developing simulations, etc)A passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced
                environment and hands-on design and developmentUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusMS or PhD in a signal
                processing field (digital communications, image processing, audio processing, ML/AI, etc)3 years
                experience working on software defined radios or modem ASICsExperience with PythonExperience with GNU
                RadioExperience with radio test planning, automation and executionExperience with multi-rate signal
                processing techniques (polyphase filter banks, resampling techniques)Experience with RTL development
                (and/or embedded C)Experience with fixed point implementation (managing precision, quantization noise,
                underflow, overflow, unit testing, etc)Experience with PA linearizationExperience with multi-antenna
                systems (beamforming, MIMO)Experience with DVB-S2/x, DVB-RCS2 standardsExperience with Satellite radio
                systems (ground segment and/or space segment)Apply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>3502487173</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Electrical Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astraniselectrical-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Electrical EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR
                GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make
                exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We
                are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world
                online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with
                incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves
                fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real
                hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products
                are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other
                distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join
                our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDesign circuits + PCBs for
                various spacecraft subsystemsTest + validate hardware systems across the spacecraftAssist with low level
                software to interface with various spacecraft subsystemsRequirementsB.S. or M.S. in electrical or
                computer engineering, or equivalent technical degree A passion for hardware development, including
                working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and developmentDemonstrated ability to
                personally design, build, and test hardware from scratchStrong analog/mixed-signal circuit design
                skillsExperience with debugging circuits with embedded software, from oscilloscope to firmwareUS
                Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with Python programmingExperience with automated HW
                testingExperience with electromechanical elementsKnowledge of radiation effects on semiconductorsView
                our other jobs here https://jobs.lever.co/astranisApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>3861560880</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Electrical Engineer - Power Electronics</job_title>
            <job_slug>astraniselectrical-engineer-power-electronics2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Electrical Engineer - Power ElectronicsSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this
                jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are
                unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to
                change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to
                bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleLead the design of
                kW-level power systems for our satellitesManage and control key components such as solar panel arrays,
                power regulation and distribution, and high-density batteriesIntegrate these systems into the spacecraft
                by working closely with the rest of the teamRequirementsBachelor of Science degree in Electrical
                Engineering or equivalentA passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced
                environment and hands-on design and developmentExperience in designing, building, and testing analog and
                digital circuitsExperience with kW level power electronics and galvanic isolationExperience with
                photovoltaics and MPPTsExperience with Li-ion batteries and chargersExperience with PCB thermal
                considerationsExperience with magnetics in power electronicsMastery of electrical CADUS Citizenship or
                Green CardBonusExperience with designing for fault tolerance, especially to withstand a radiation
                environmentExperience with design, layout, and bring-up of large chips, including 1000 pin BGA MCUs and
                FPGAsExperience with power distribution networks for high frequency applicationsFamiliarity with
                embedded programmingElectromechanical design experienceEMI/EMC experienceApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>2875414776</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Electrical Engineer - Radio Hardware</job_title>
            <job_slug>astraniselectrical-engineer-radio-hardware2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Electrical Engineer - Radio HardwareSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this
                jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are
                unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to
                change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to
                bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleWork on the full suite of
                radio hardwareDesign and test ultra high speed digital data systemsWork with state of the art FPGAs and
                data convertersDesign and lay out PCBs to implement these systemsTest and validate full radio signal
                chainIntegrate these systems into the spacecraft by working closely with the rest of the
                teamRequirementsB.S. or M.S. in electrical or computer engineering, or equivalent technical degree A
                passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and
                developmentDemonstrated ability to personally design, build, and test hardware from scratchExperience
                with Altium or similar EDA toolsExperience with high-density PCB designExperience designing high speed
                clock treesStrong analog/mixed-signal circuit design skillsComfortable working with full RF signal
                chainUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusFamiliarity with radio nonidealities (HD, IMD, IQ imbalance, gain
                ripple, group delay distortion)Familiarity with data converter nonidealities (INL, DNL, HD, quantization
                noise)Familiarity with high speed SERDES protocols (double bonus: JESD204B)Experience with RF test +
                measurement equipment Experience with high speed bench equipment (VNA, TDR, BERT, etc)Experience with
                MentorGraphics HyperLynx, Cadence Sigrity, Ansys HFSS or similar signal integrity toolsExperience
                modeling trace/interconnect loss and compensationApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>2871064328</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Electrical Engineer - Senior Avionics Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astraniselectrical-engineer-senior-avionics-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Electrical Engineer - Senior Avionics EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply
                for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we
                are unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going
                to change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites
                to bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleArchitect, design, and
                develop space tolerant electronics that will support the functions of our satellites.Ownership of
                spacecraft avionics systems.Work within a multidisciplinary team to design and execute for satellite
                avionics.Duties include program management, subsystem design, analysis, debugging, and hardware bug
                tracking.Support through production and test.RequirementsB.S. or higher in electrical or computer
                engineering, or similar technical degree 5+ years of professional experience with fast-paced product
                design cycles5+ years of board level experience designing hardware from concept through production.A
                passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and
                developmentDemonstrated ability to design, build, and test hardware from scratchStrong
                analog/mixed-signal circuit design skillsUS Citizenship or Green CardBonus5+ years of experience with
                designing and implementing signal conditioning, sensors, electro-mechanical actuators, power switches,
                embedded computers, or such hardware.Experience with FPGAs, Microcontrollers, and communication schemes
                (RS-485, SPI, Ethernet, I2C)Experience leading a team of engineers and working with teams in other
                disciplines. Strong understanding of computers and knowledge of C, C++, or PythonRadiation effects
                knowledgeEnvironmental test experienceApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>2973238716</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Electrical Engineer - Signal Integrity</job_title>
            <job_slug>astraniselectrical-engineer-signal-integrity2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Electrical Engineer - Signal IntegritySan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this
                jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are
                unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to
                change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to
                bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDesign and validate ultra
                high speed digital data systemsSelect PCB stackups and help with PDN designs for other systemsChoose
                electrical harnesses for use in harsh environmentsIntegrate these systems into the spacecraft by working
                closely with the rest of the teamRequirementsB.S. or M.S. in electrical or computer engineering, or
                equivalent technical degree A passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced
                environment and hands-on design and developmentExperience modeling trace/interconnect loss and
                compensationExperience designing for EMI/EMC Experience with MentorGraphics HyperLynx, Cadence Sigrity,
                Ansys HFSS or other signal integrity toolsExperience with Altium or similar EDA toolsExperience with
                high speed bench equipment [VNA, TDR, BERT, etc]US Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with
                high-density PCB layoutExperience with Xilinx FPGAsExperience with serial [SerDes] protocols Experience
                with PythonApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>2347364610</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Engineering Ops: Systems Engineering</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisengineering-ops-systems-engineering2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Engineering Ops: Systems EngineeringSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this
                jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are
                unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to
                change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to
                bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleAcquire and maintain
                understanding of spacecraft design and all interfaces, internal and externalManage requirements,
                flowdowns, and verifications across many subsystems, including ground and space segmentsIdentify,
                reconcile, and head off conflicts across interdependent subsystem designs, teams, and interfacesTrack
                many different aspects of the system requirements, including verification and validation, flowdown, and
                non-compliancesDevise Failure Modes and Effects Criticality Analyses (FMECA)Promote best practices
                relating to system design, requirements elicitation, configuration control, human and system safety,
                testability, operability, reliability, and more.RequirementsB.S. or M.S. in aerospace, electrical,
                computer, or mechanical engineering, or equivalent technical degreeExperience with space system
                requirements managementExperience with configuration managementFluency with Jira or other issue tracking
                systemsExperience with system-level budgets (mass/power/pointing/etc.) and ability to highlight
                inconsistencies and optimizationsUnderstanding of space program milestonesExperience with solving
                interdisciplinary technical problemsTechnical expertise in at least one spacecraft design subsystem
                areaUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with Python programmingExperience with automated HW
                testingExperience with debugging circuits with embedded software, from oscilloscope to
                firmwareExperience with electromechanical systemsExperience designing electrical and/or mechanical test
                and assembly fixturingDirect experience in operating satellitesApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>3491815392</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>FPGA Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisfpga-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>FPGA EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN
                CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make exceptions.)Four
                billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We are building the
                next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world online. And to
                pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with incredibly smart
                people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space
                experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real hardware and be ok with
                struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the
                whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a
                diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their
                unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDesign RTL for high data rate, software defined
                radiosWork with multiple FPGAs and toolchainsInterface FPGAs with high speed data converters, memories,
                MCUsDesign, implement and test radiation mitigation schemes on FPGACollaborate closely with DSP/radio
                algorithm designerCollaborate closely with embedded firmware and software engineersRequirementsUS
                Citizenship or Green Card (This is a legal requirement; no exceptions)Bachelor of Science degree in
                electrical engineering, computer science, computer engineering, or equivalentA passion for hardware
                development, including working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and developmentExperience
                in designing, implementing, and testing high throughput systems implemented on FPGAsStrong proficiency
                with Verilog (preferably SystemVerilog) for both synthesis and verificationExperience with modern
                communication systems (RF, IF/IQ, time/freq domains, modulation)BonusMS or PhD in computer engineering
                or equivalentConsiderable expertise in at least 1 domain beyond just the logic design. This could be
                DSP/radio design, software, hi-rel design (e.g. fault analysis &amp; recover), etc.Experience with
                Xilinx FPGAs Experience with Vivado IDE, TCLFamiliarity with system level estimates and implications of
                power, thermal, and real estateExperience with high speed data converters (ADCs, DACs,
                JESD204B)Experience with circuit level debuggingExperience with digital communication theory and
                implementation, such as LDPC implementationsExperience with space-based systemsApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1720280674</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Guidance, Navigation, and Control Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisguidance-navigation-and-control-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Guidance, Navigation, and Control EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for
                this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are
                unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to
                change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to
                bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleWork with the Guidance,
                Navigation, and Control team to design, build, test, and operate satellite hardware and softwareSystem
                design including make/buy trades, component selection, system sizing, and pointing budgetsHardware
                development including managing internal component build, external vendors, and subassembly bring-up and
                testingSoftware development including simulation framework, environmental models, and flight
                algorithmsValidation and verification through software simulation, Monte Carlo analysis, and hardware in
                the loop testingIntegration and test supportConcept of operations development, mission planning, and
                flight operation supportRequirementsBachelor of Science degree in a technical discipline (e.g.
                engineering, CS, physics) with a focus on control systems, orbital mechanics, or similarDemonstrated
                experience in developing, implementing, and testing control systemsFamiliarity with processing sensor
                data and with sensor fusion techniques (e.g. extended Kalman filters) Demonstrated experience in
                developing 6-DOF simulationsA passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced
                environment and doing hands-on design/developmentDemonstrated ability to personally design, build, and
                test hardware and/or software from scratchUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience implementing
                algorithms for embedded systems in C++ or similarExperience with NumPy, SciPyExperience with spacecraft
                control systemsExperience with low thrust trajectories Experience with geostationary spacecraft
                operations Experience with spacecraft propulsionExperience with hardware in the loop simulationApply for
                this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>2123494191</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>IT System Administrator</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisit-system-administrator2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>IT System AdministratorSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS
                CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to
                make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change
                that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring
                the world online.IT systems support everything we do at Astranis. We are a well-funded team that moves
                fast, and are looking for people who are scrappy, creative, ambitious, and who want to make an impact in
                the world. This role offers a huge amount of room to work collaboratively with engineers across a wide
                range of disciplines and to grow in scope as we scale up our satellite operations.We offer competitive
                salary, excellent healthcare, and lunch delivered to the office every day.Our mission and our products
                are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other
                distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join
                our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.The RoleInstall, configure, manage,
                and monitor networks, storage, and access - locally and in the cloudDefine corporate security policies
                and procedures, and aid in implementing themDevelop and implement a comprehensive data backup
                strategyDocument IT infrastructure, policies, and proceduresWrite scripts to automate routine
                tasksAdminister systems spanning multiple operating systems (Windows, MacOS, Linux)Collaborate with
                other team members to address IT challenges as they arise -- we are a tech-savvy team, and user support
                is expected to be minimalRequirementsStrong background in network engineering / IT
                administrationExcellent written and oral communication skillsExperience administering wired and wireless
                networks, VPNs, and cloud-based servicesExperience with high-level scripting languages like Bash,
                Python, or PowerShellUS Citizenship or Green CardBonus if you have experience with one or more of the
                followingAmazon Web ServicesDocker instancesNetwork monitoring and alerting toolsUbiquiti networking
                gearFlexNet/FlexLMAtlassian (Jira, Confluence)Writing internal self-service toolsApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>178550826</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Mechanical Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranismechanical-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Mechanical EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR
                GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make
                exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We
                are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world
                online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with
                incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves
                fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real
                hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products
                are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other
                distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join
                our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDesign, analyze, procure,
                assemble, and test primary structure, bracketry, and mechanisms for Astranis spacecraft. Components
                include composite and metallic parts and assemblies with a variety of manufacturing techniques.Develop
                requirements for components and systems including loads, interfaces, and functional requirements.Perform
                mechanical and thermal analysis for spacecraft systemsIntegrate parts and systems into the spacecraft by
                working closely with the rest of the team, and document and develop procedures to improve the build
                process in the future.RequirementsBachelor of Science degree in mechanical engineering or
                equivalentMastery of mechanical CADDemonstrated fundamentals with mechanical and thermal analytic
                abilities; FEA experience is not required, but preferredA passion for hardware development, including
                working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and developmentUS Citizenship or Green
                CardBonusExperience with mechanical and/or thermal FEAExperience with composite structuresExperience in
                designing in a vacuum environment with large temperature swingsExperience with vibration
                environmentsElectromechanical design experienceApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1901394981</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Propulsion Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranispropulsion-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Propulsion EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR
                GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make
                exceptions.)We&#8217;re building small, low-cost telecommunications satellites. Our mission is to help
                bring the 4 billion people online who are without internet. And to pull it off we have to reinvent
                microwave radio systems in space using software-defined radios.Work with incredibly smart people who
                have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space experience
                needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real hardware and be ok with struggling to
                do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the whole world
                and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse and
                inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their unique
                perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDesign, build, test, and operate geostationary satellite
                monopropellant and electric propulsion systems System sizing Component selection Vendor
                managementAnalysis including plume impingement, water hammer, pressure drop, and thermalTest plan
                generationConcept of operation developmentRequirementsBachelor of Science degree in a technical
                discipline (e.g. engineering, physics)3+ years of industry experience with spacecraft
                propulsionDemonstrated experience in designing, implementing, testing, and operating spacecraft
                propulsion systemsA passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced environment and
                doing hands-on design/developmentUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with low thrust
                trajectories Experience with geostationary spacecraft operations Experience with small satellites Apply
                for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>2190681927</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>RF Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisrf-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>RF EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN
                CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make exceptions.)Four
                billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We are building the
                next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world online. And to
                pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with incredibly smart
                people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space
                experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real hardware and be ok with
                struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the
                whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a
                diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their
                unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDesign, simulate, implement, and measure passive/active
                RF sub-systems at microwave frequencies, including; LNAs, power amplifiers, up/down convertors,
                oscillators, antennas, etc. Integrate these systems into the spacecraft by working closely with the rest
                of the teamRequirementsPassion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced environment
                and hands-on design and developmentDeep knowledge of basic RF concepts, such as transmission lines,
                impedance matching, and filter designHands-on experience in designing, building, and testing RF hardware
                for microwave frequenciesExperience with RF simulation toolsUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusMS or PhD
                in electrical engineering, physics, applied physics, or equivalentAntennas and Electromagnetics
                propagation knowledge and backgroundExperience with Software Defined Radios and associated
                skillsetExperience with PCB design, layout and simulationApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>3515857305</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Software Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranissoftware-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Software EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR
                GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make
                exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We
                are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world
                online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with
                incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves
                fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real
                hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products
                are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other
                distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join
                our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.The Role (one or more of)Implement
                spacecraft avionics softwareImplement ground control and telemetry softwareImplement software for
                automated testing at component, functional and system levels, including HITL (Hardware in the Loop)
                testingImplement low level software to interface with various spacecraft
                componentsImplement/troubleshoot/improve real time operating system componentsRequirementsBachelor of
                Science degree in CS, EE (or equivalent background knowledge)A passion for building things, including
                working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and developmentExperience with C and/or
                C++Experience with Python (or other high-level OO scripting language(s))Experience with Linux and shell
                command line toolsUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with designing real time systemsExperience
                with building bare-metal embedded system softwareExperience with reading schematics and datasheets,
                debugging circuits that interface with embedded software, from debugger to logic analyzer to
                oscilloscopeExperience with web development frameworks and databasesExperience with test framework
                development, especially with HITL (Hardware in the Loop) systemsOur software work spans many areas, from
                embedded work on small microcontrollers, to numerical algorithms running on flight computers, to
                telemetry processing, querying and display on ground systems.We are looking for talented software
                generalists - people who are excited and able to contribute to more than one area.Apply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>2351834848</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Spacecraft Systems Test Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisspacecraft-systems-test-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Spacecraft Systems Test EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS
                CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to
                make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change
                that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring
                the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleWork with design engineers
                to develop and execute test plans and procedures for spacecraft components at all levels of assembly,
                including fully-built, flight-ready spacecraftAnalyze and draw conclusions from test resultsTroubleshoot
                test failuresOperate test equipment, manage test facilities, and troubleshoot test failures and
                breakdownsDesign electrical and/or mechanical fixturing to support component testsRequirementsB.S. in
                electrical engineering, computer engineering, computer science, or equivalent technical degreeExperience
                developing spacecraft component and assembly test plans/proceduresExperience executing environmental
                tests on spacecraft and componentsExperience with test data acquisition, storage, processing, and
                presentationAbility to design and lay out printed circuit boards to support testingAbility to design and
                manufacture mechanical test fixtures and skill gathering requirements from design engineersComfort with
                adapting to and overcoming test failures, and capturing lessons learned from themExperience with an
                object oriented programming language (bonus for Python skill in test equipment interfaces or data
                analysis)US Citizenship or Green CardBonusStrong analog/mixed-signal circuit skillsKnowledge of
                radiation effects on semiconductorsExperience with automated bench testingExperience with
                electromechanical systemsExperience with testing in space environmentsApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1645938842</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Thermal Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisthermal-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Thermal EngineerSan Francisco, CAEngineeringFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR
                GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make
                exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We
                are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world
                online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with
                incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves
                fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real
                hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.This posting is for applicants
                who are primarily interested in design, analysis, and development of thermal solutions for spacecraft,
                including the primary structures, thermal coatings, and electronics enclosures. However, we encourage
                everyone to broaden their skillsets and the nature of the small company work means that you'd be
                involved on a number of different projects.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the whole
                world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse
                and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their unique
                perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDevelop thermal loading, nominal and off-nominal analysis cases
                and component temperature limits for Astranis spacecraft in conjunction with the rest of the teamBuild
                complex submodels as necessary and simplified representations for the top level thermal modelDesign,
                analyze, procure and test thermal solutions such as strapping and heat pipes, both as samples and as
                part of primary structureDevelop processes and procedures for integration and assembly which ensure
                thermal design intent is metPlan and run thermal vacuum testing and verification for the
                spacecraftRequirementsBachelor of Science degree in engineeringExperience in thermal analysis and
                thermally-constrained design; computational thermal design experience (finite methods) is not required
                but highly preferredProficiency with mechanical CADA passion for hardware development, including working
                in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and developmentUS Citizenship or Green
                CardBonusExperience with Thermal DesktopExperience with FEMAP/NastranExperience with composite
                structuresExperience in designing in a vacuum environment with large temperature swingsApply for this
                job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1860166775</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Intern - Communications/DSP Engineer [Fall 19, Spring 20]</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisintern-communicationsdsp-engineer-fall-19-spring-202019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Intern - Communications/DSP Engineer [Fall 19, Spring 20]San Francisco,
                CAInternshipsInternApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US
                export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to
                the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We are building the next generation of smaller,
                lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to
                reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown
                things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you
                just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things
                that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone
                in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive
                workplace, and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their unique perspective to help
                make us stronger.RoleWork with a small team of signal processing/communications engineers to develop and
                implement various radio functions (filtering, gain control, frequency tracking, digital
                upconversion/downconversion, linearization, timing and phase recovery, equalization, FEC, symbol
                mapping/demapping, framing, etc )Work closely with FPGA developers to implement, test and debug all
                radio functions on real hardwareRequirementsStrong fundamentals in "signals and systems" (basic
                transforms, aliasing, analysis in both continuous and discrete domains, interpolation, decimation, etc)
                Experience with digital communication theory and application (modulation, coding)Experience with testing
                and debugging radio hardware (signal generator, signal analyzer, network analyzer, oscilloscope)Strong
                RF fundamentals (amplifiers, antennas, analog filters, channel effects, distortions, etc)Strong
                software/firmware fundamentals (experience writing firmware for DSP/MCU/FPGA, scripting, simulation,
                etc)A passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on
                design and developmentUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with software defined radiosExperience
                with PythonExperience with GNU RadioExperience with FPGA development (and/or embedded C)Experience with
                test planning, automation and executionApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1438772941</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Intern - Electrical Engineering (Fall 2019)</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisintern-electrical-engineering-fall-20192019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Intern - Electrical Engineering (Fall 2019)San Francisco, CAInternshipsInternApply for this
                jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are
                unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to
                change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to
                bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleThis posting covers
                working with the payload, avionics, and power systems teams at AstranisWork on a hardware engineering
                team to build and test flight hardwareDesign stress test equipment to validate designs across a wide
                range of conditionsWrite code to help evaluate performance and automate testing of satellite
                hardwareRequirementsCurrently pursuing a B.S. or M.S. in electrical or computer engineering, or
                equivalent technical degree A passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced
                environment and hands-on design and developmentDemonstrated ability to personally design, build, and
                test hardware from scratchUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with Altium Designer (or other PCB
                design software)Experience with SPICE-based simulators (ADS, LTSpice, SIMPLIS)Experience with Python or
                MATLABExperience with C/C++Experience with RF bench equipment (VNAs, Spectrum Analyzers, Signal
                Generators)Apply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>589402943</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Intern - FPGA Engineer</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisintern-fpga-engineer2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Intern - FPGA EngineerSan Francisco, CAInternshipsInternApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR
                GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make
                exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We
                are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world
                online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with
                incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves
                fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real
                hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products
                are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other
                distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join
                our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDesign RTL for high data rate,
                software defined radiosWork with multiple FPGAs and toolchainsInterface FPGAs with high speed data
                converters, memories, MCUsDesign, implement and test radiation mitigation schemes on FPGACollaborate
                closely with DSP/radio algorithm designerCollaborate closely with embedded firmware and software
                engineersRequirementsUS Citizenship or Green Card (This is a legal requirement; no exceptions)Currently
                pursuing a B.S. or M.S. in electrical engineering, computer science, computer engineering, or
                equivalentA passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on
                design and developmentExperience in designing, implementing, and testing high throughput systems
                implemented on FPGAsProficiency with Verilog/SystemVerilog for synthesisBonusExperience with UVM and
                advanced SystemVerilog verificationExperience with Xilinx FPGAs Experience with Vivado IDE,
                TCLFamiliarity with system level estimates and implications of power, thermal, and real estateExperience
                with high speed data converters (ADCs, DACs, JESD204B)Experience with circuit level debuggingExperience
                with digital communication theory and implementation, such as LDPC implementationsExperience with
                space-based systemsExperience with modern communication systems (RF, IF/IQ, time/freq domains,
                modulation)Experience in at least 1 domain beyond logic design. This could be DSP/radio design,
                software, hi-rel design (e.g. fault analysis &amp; recover), etc.Please note that we are full for
                summer. Interns will only be considered for Fall / Spring.Apply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>128993954</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Intern - Guidance, Navigation, and Control (Fall 2019)</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisintern-guidance-navigation-and-control-fall-20192019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Intern - Guidance, Navigation, and Control (Fall 2019)San Francisco,
                CAInternshipsInternApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US
                export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to
                the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We are building the next generation of smaller,
                lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to
                reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown
                things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you
                just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things
                that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone
                in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive
                workplace, and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their unique perspective to help
                make us stronger.RoleWork with the Guidance, Navigation, and Control team to design, build, and test
                satellite hardware and softwareRequirementsCurrently pursuing a B.S. or M.S. in a technical discipline
                (e.g. engineering, CS, physics) with a focus on control systems, orbital mechanics, or spacecraft
                propulsionFamiliarity with classical control theoryExperience with python or C/C++Demonstrated ability
                to personally design, build, and test hardware and/or software from scratchUS Citizenship or Green
                CardBonusFamiliarity with spacecraft designExperience with low thrust trajectoriesApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>506948861</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Intern - Mechanical Engineering (Spring &amp; Fall 2019)</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisintern-mechanical-engineering-spring-fall-20192019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Intern - Mechanical Engineering (Spring &amp; Fall 2019)San Francisco,
                CAInternshipsInternApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US
                export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make exceptions.)Summer and Winter/Spring 2019 slots have
                been filled at this time; we are only accepting or Fall/Winter 2019 applications.Four billion people do
                not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We are building the next generation
                of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world online. And to pull it off we
                have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have
                flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space experience
                needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real hardware and be ok with struggling to
                do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the whole world
                and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse and
                inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their unique
                perspective to help make us stronger.RoleWork with the engineering team to design, build, and test
                satellite hardware and/or software.RequirementsCurrently pursuing a B.S. or M.S. in mechanical,
                aerospace, or equivalent technical degree (e.g. physics or applied math)A passion for hardware
                development, including working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and
                developmentDemonstrated ability to personally design, build, and test hardware from scratchUS
                Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with CADExperience with analytical software such as stress or
                thermal analysisExperience with electromechanical system design and specificationExperience with control
                system modeling and designApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1323473267</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Intern - RF Engineering</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisintern-rf-engineering2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Intern - RF EngineeringSan Francisco, CAInternshipsInternApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP
                OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make
                exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We
                are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world
                online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with
                incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves
                fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real
                hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our products
                are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other
                distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join
                our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleDesign, simulate, implement,
                and measure passive/active RF sub-systems at microwave frequencies, including; LNAs, power amplifiers,
                up/down convertors, oscillators, etc. Integrate these systems into the spacecraft by working closely
                with the rest of the teamRequirementsPassion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced
                environment and hands-on design and developmentDeep knowledge of basic RF concepts, such as transmission
                lines, impedance matching, and filter designHands-on experience in designing, building, and testing RF
                hardware for microwave frequenciesExperience with RF simulation toolsUS Citizenship or Green
                CardBonusAntennas and Electromagnetics propagation knowledge and backgroundExperience with Software
                Defined RadiosExperience with high speed ADCs and DACsExperience with PCB designExperience with FPGA/DSP
                programmingApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1453924407</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Intern - Software Engineering</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisintern-software-engineering2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Intern - Software EngineeringSan Francisco, CAInternshipsInternApply for this jobUS
                CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED.(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to
                make exceptions.)All Summer 2019 internship positions have been filled. We are currently accepting
                applications for Spring/Fall 2019 internships.Four billion people do not have access to the internet.
                Astranis is going to change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost
                telecommunications satellites to bring the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent
                microwave radio systems in space using SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in
                space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need
                to enjoy getting your hands dirty with real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem
                impossibly hard.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it,
                regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace,
                and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us
                stronger.The RoleWork with the engineering team to design, write and test software (embedded software
                running on satellites, as well as variety of ground control and testing software)RequirementsCurrently
                pursuing a B.S. or M.S. in Computer Science, Electrical or Computer Engineering, or equivalent technical
                degreeExperience with C/C++ and scripting language(s)Demonstrated ability to personally design, write,
                and test software from scratchUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with embedded systems running
                on bare metalExperience with real time operating systemsExperience with FPGA or DSP programmingNote: All
                Summer 2019 internship positions have been filled. We are currently accepting applications for
                Spring/Fall 2019 internships.Apply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1788310327</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Director of HR</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisdirector-of-hr2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Director of HRSan Francisco, CAOperations and Business StrategyFull-timeApply for this
                jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are
                unable to make exceptions.)&#160;Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is
                going to change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications
                satellites to bring the world online. &#160;Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in
                space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need
                to enjoy getting your hands dirty and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.&#160;Our
                mission and our products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race,
                creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all
                people to come join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleManage the
                work flows, transactions, reporting, and record keeping aspects of our people function, including
                payroll, benefits, and compliance.Provide expertise and guidance on employment practices, legal
                compliance, company policies, etc.Ensure HR operational excellence with accurate, timely, and robust
                information, process, and project management practices.Champion and role model our culture, values, and
                mission, finding ways to continually strengthen them at the company overall.Scale professional
                development programs to help our employees build their skill sets, driving employee retention and
                satisfaction. Manage and expand our diversity and inclusion initiative.Manage the full lifecycle of an
                employee from developing new hire onboarding and offboarding processes.Requirements8+ years working in
                HR/People OperationsExperience working in fast paced, high growth, dynamic companiesExtremely organized
                and detail-oriented; you love bringing order out of chaosDeeply caring with strong interpersonal skills;
                helping others make you smileEnergized by finding opportunities to improve processes through technology
                and designKnowledgeable in CA and US HR-related policies and law, and fluent in HR systems, tools and
                applicationsEntrepreneurial drive; we are a small start-up that requires the ability to roll up your
                sleeves and jump inAbility to maintain confidentiality of sensitive informationUS Citizenship or Green
                CardApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>1392712037</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Lab Manager</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranislab-manager2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Lab ManagerSan Francisco, CAOperations and Business StrategyFull-timeApply for this jobUS
                CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are unable to
                make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to change
                that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring
                the world online. And to pull it off we have to reinvent microwave radio systems in space using
                SDRs.Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team
                that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty with
                real hardware and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleLab organization and
                management, and workflow design (for R&amp;D and Production cleanroom)Creating and enforcing lab
                procedures and cleanliness/organization standardsLab equipment purchasing, management, maintenance, and
                rentalsInventory managementManufacturing operations and quality assuranceChampion inter-departmental,
                work instruction, bringup, and test processes and procedures while also driving efficiencies, quality
                compliance, and continuous improvementRequirementsB.S. or M.S. in engineering, or equivalent technical
                degreeStart-up mentality -- ability to work in both managerial and individual contributor roles
                (willingness to do whatever is needed)Develop and champion structured Product Development disciplines
                within the prototype/production manufacturing function, ensure the Change Management processes are well
                understood, and used, throughout the organizationChampion inter-departmental processes and procedures,
                driving efficiencies, quality compliance, and continuous improvementExperience with space or other high-
                reliability hardwareExperience with Thermal Vacuum, and Vibration, instrumentation and test processesA
                passion for hardware development, including working in a fast-paced environment and hands-on design and
                developmentDemonstrated ability to manage lab and/or production facility facilities, equipment, and
                operationsStrong organizational skills and attention to detailAbility to handle multiple tasks and
                prioritizeStrong communication skillsUS Citizenship or Green CardBonusExperience with Python
                programmingExperience with automated HW testingExperience with RF test and measurementExperience with
                high speed digital test and measurementExperience with metrologyView our other jobs here
                https://jobs.lever.co/astranisApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>3006547832</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Operations Manager &#8212; People Operations</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranisoperations-manager-people-operations2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Operations Manager &#8212; People OperationsSan Francisco, CAOperations and Business
                StrategyFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export
                regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make exceptions.)&#160;Four billion people do not have access to
                the internet. Astranis is going to change that. We are building the next generation of smaller,
                lower-cost telecommunications satellites to bring the world online.&#160;&#160;Work with incredibly
                smart people who have flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior
                space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty and be ok with struggling to do
                things that seem impossibly hard.&#160;Our mission and our products are meant to connect the whole world
                and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse and
                inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their unique
                perspective to help make us stronger.RoleManage the work flows, transactions, reporting, and record
                keeping aspects of our people function, including payroll, benefits, and compliance.Provide expertise
                and guidance on employment practices, legal compliance, company policies, etc.Ensure HR operational
                excellence with accurate, timely, and robust information, process, and project management
                practices.Champion and role model our culture, values, and mission, finding ways to continually
                strengthen them at the company overall.Scale professional development programs to help our employees
                build their skill sets, driving employee retention and satisfaction.&#160;Manage and expand our
                diversity and inclusion initiative.Manage the full lifecycle of an employee from developing new hire
                onboarding and offboarding processes.Requirements5+ years working in HR/People OperationsExperience
                working in fast paced, high growth, dynamic companiesExtremely organized and detail-oriented; you love
                bringing order out of chaosDeeply caring with strong interpersonal skills; helping others make you
                smileEnergized by finding opportunities to improve processes through technology and designKnowledgeable
                in CA and US HR-related policies and law, and fluent in HR systems, tools and
                applicationsEntrepreneurial drive; we are a small start-up that requires the ability to roll up your
                sleeves and jump inAbility to maintain confidentiality of sensitive informationUS Citizenship or Green
                CardApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>3930272847</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Supply Chain and Procurement Manager</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranissupply-chain-and-procurement-manager2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Supply Chain and Procurement ManagerSan Francisco, CAOperations and Business
                StrategyFull-timeApply for this jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export
                regulations. Sorry, we are unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the
                internet. Astranis is going to change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost
                telecommunications satellites to bring the world online.&#160;Work with incredibly smart people who have
                flown things in space before. We are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space experience
                needed, you just need to enjoy getting your hands dirty and be ok with struggling to do things that seem
                impossibly hard.Our mission and our products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it,
                regardless of race, creed, or any other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace,
                and we encourage all people to come join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us
                stronger.RoleResponsible for the &#8220;life cycle&#8221; of component procurement, from the earliest
                stages of vendor selection all the way to when the component is being installed in the spacecraftDevelop
                and maintain strong supplier relationshipsVisit supplier&#8217;s facilities and accurately assess
                technical capability, equipment, and capacityWork with engineering teams on sourcing strategy, supplier
                roadmaps, market analysis and conducting design and cost trade-off analysis to ensure quality, pricing,
                and delivery standardsSource, negotiate, and purchase components across every satellite subsystem Place
                purchase orders for material requirement planning messages for production partsConsistently monitor and
                maintain necessary inventory levels to production demandsEstablish systems to minimize discrepancies and
                ensure accuracy and thoroughness throughout the procurement life cycleRequirementsBachelor's degree in
                engineering, business, supply chain, or a similar discipline3+ years of work experience in procurement,
                manufacturing, or related supply chain disciplinesIncredibly detail-oriented &#8212; the type of person
                who loves high-volume logistics and is hyper-organizedExperience with manufacturing of electronic and/or
                mechanical componentsExperience with enterprise resource planning and inventory / asset management
                systemsAbility to read technical drawings and datasheetsAbility to effectively communicate with
                engineering teamsExcellent negotiation, written and verbal skillsUS Citizenship or Green CardApply for
                this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
        <job>
            <id>3264800262</id>
            <employer_id>2</employer_id>
            <company_name>Astranis</company_name>
            <company_url>www.astranis.com</company_url>
            <company_email>test@astranis.com</company_email>
            <job_title>Technical Recruiter</job_title>
            <job_slug>astranistechnical-recruiter2019-05-20</job_slug>
            <job_description>Technical RecruiterSan Francisco, CAOperations and Business StrategyFull-timeApply for this
                jobUS CITIZENSHIP OR GREEN CARD REQUIRED(Note: this is due to US export regulations. Sorry, we are
                unable to make exceptions.)Four billion people do not have access to the internet. Astranis is going to
                change that. We are building the next generation of smaller, lower-cost telecommunications satellites to
                bring the world online.&#160;Work with incredibly smart people who have flown things in space before. We
                are a well-funded team that moves fast. No prior space experience needed, you just need to enjoy getting
                your hands dirty and be ok with struggling to do things that seem impossibly hard.Our mission and our
                products are meant to connect the whole world and everyone in it, regardless of race, creed, or any
                other distinction. We believe in a diverse and inclusive workplace, and we encourage all people to come
                join our team and bring their unique perspective to help make us stronger.RoleRecruit top-tier
                engineering and business talent at a rapidly-growing company.Provide a great candidate experience
                throughout every step of the interview process.Screen applicants, coordinate onsite interviews, and
                conduct reference checks.Build strong pipelines and proactively source passive candidates.Manage and
                expand our diversity and inclusion initiative.Collect and analyze data on our recruiting funnel, and
                make recommendations about how to improve our processes.Requirements5+ years experience as a recruiter
                at a fast paced, high growth technology company &#8212; bonus if it's a hardware companyProven abilities
                to attract passive candidates and build a diverse pipelineAbility to distinguish between the top 50% and
                the top 5% of talent within their respective fieldsExcellent verbal and written communication skills,
                with an appropriate blend of professionalism and friendlinessCreative candidate sourcing techniques and
                data driven decision makingExceptional organizational skills and great follow-through on tasksUS
                Citizenship or Green CardApply for this job
            </job_description>
            <job_country>840</job_country>
            <job_state>CA</job_state>
            <job_city>San Francisco</job_city>
            <job_created_at>2019-05-20</job_created_at>
            <job_expires_at>2019-05-23</job_expires_at>
            <is_active>1</is_active>
            <is_approved>0</is_approved>
            <is_filled>0</is_filled>
            <is_featured>0</is_featured>
        </job>
    </jobs>
</wpjb>
