<wpjb>
  <jobs>
    <job>
      <id>993656934</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3629097176</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2222292672</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3604213709</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2274335496</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1164872666</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>226914593</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>929387851</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Avionics Systems Analysis Engineer (Dragon)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexavionics-systems-analysis-engineer-dragon2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
AVIONICS SYSTEMS ANALYSIS ENGINEER (DRAGON)
As an avionics systems engineer you will be responsible for bridging low level design to high level vehicle operations and requirements. These responsibilities include both systems analysis and systems test. As an analyst, you will be responsible for modeling the electrical and power systems on the spacecraft to ensure the system can complete all mission objectives. As a test engineer, you will be responsible for testing fault conditions and ensuring compatibility of sub-component and sub-systems.
You will own all aspects of validation including testing and analysis during development through to final verification and certification for launch. The unforgiving environments of launch and space travel require flawless execution with layers of fault tolerance to handle fault scenarios. Your creativity and relentless commitment to quality will be a key component to building the safest and most reliable space vehicles. Our fundamental goal is to allow humanity to explore the stars; with it comes extreme responsibility to ensure the safety of the crew and payload. Are you up for the challenge?
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Develop, execute, and maintain test plans, analysis and test code for the systems that fly our rockets and spacecraft
Develop electrical models and simulations for the vehicle avionics systems, including mission power budgets, power control systems, and power stability analysis
Analyze test results and bugs that require in-depth investigations
Hands-on integration and troubleshooting on flight representative hardware and vehicle systems
Become an expert at all aspects that impact the system under validation from software execution to avionics control to propulsion systems
Act as the focal point and for risk analysis and support for issue resolution and change impact
Verify avionics system test coverage on fight or flight-representative hardware and validate the vehicle is &#8220;go for launch&#8221;
Participate in the design cycle as required to improve design for reliability, operations, and testability

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in an engineering discipline
1+ years of experience in system design, integration, or test of complex systems

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

2+ years of professional experience leading electrical integration and test operations of complex systems
Experience developing models and simulations of complex electrical and power systems
Experience leading electrical integration and test operations on rockets, satellites, planetary exploration spacecraft, ships, or aircraft
Experience designing/operating and building autonomous fault-tolerant robotic systems
Ability to assess risk and make design and development recommendations without all available data
Ability to work in a fast paced, autonomously driven, and demanding atmosphere
Competence with electrical test equipment (multimeters, oscilloscopes, bench power supplies)
Knowledge of and experience in analog to digital and digital to analog converters, power supply components and design, analog testing/troubleshooting techniques, and signal integrity, layout and grounding principles
Experience with control systems
Passion for advancing the commercial space industry and human spaceflight
Strong work ethic and drive to succeed with a strong sense of accountability and integrity
Excellent written and verbal communication skills

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3764681952</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Broadband Communications Integration Engineer</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexbroadband-communications-integration-engineer2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
BROADBAND COMMUNICATIONS INTEGRATION ENGINEER&#160;
As a member of the integration/test team, this position will play a critical role for integrating, testing and evaluating the functional performance, reliability and robustness of a complex satellite communication network. You will integrate the communication system components on satellite and ground station. You will explore, assess, track, and report performance status to project leaders. You will implement tools to conduct, track and improve testing processes and effectiveness. You will ensure that satellites and ground network provide the best possible communications system performance while also ensuring compliance with our operating licenses.
RESPONSIBILITIES:&#160;

Integrate communications and networking component systems.
Develop intermediate and prototype technologies to accelerate integration and development.
Create test plans, templates and strategies for block and system level tests, to test integrated broadband communications solutions for both function and performance.
Write scripts using common scripting languages.
Develop, maintain and extend test automation infrastructure.
Maintain and continuously improve test collateral and processes, continuous integration.
Execute functional testing, system testing, regression and performance testing, in the laboratory and in the field.
Configure test equipment for operation, satellite link emulator, network emulator, etc.
Interpret test automation results and track new and existing test failures.
Work with component design teams to remedy test failures and improve performance.
Prepare reports documenting test results, test coverage and other KPI metrics, and communicate issues effectively with developers and managers.
Keep abreast of latest advances in test and automation practices.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:&#160;

Bachelor's degree in computer science, computer engineering or electrical engineering.
1+ years of experience with integration and test of hardware.

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:&#160;

Master's degree in computer science, computer engineering or electrical engineering.
2+ years of professional experience with integration and test of communication systems.
5+ years of experience integrating and/or testing cellular 3G/4G/5G, WiFi, or similar protocol stacks.
5+ years of experience with Linux and Linux tools for automation.
3+ years of experience with C/C++ and Python.
Familiar with lab test equipment such as spectrum analyzers, vector signal analyzers, vector signal generator, satellite link emulator/channel emulator, network analyzers, packet load modules, and network emulators.
Demonstrable experience in script development for test automation.
Deep understanding in communication and signal processing theory.
Demonstrable experience in creating test plans and setting up test beds.
Experience with design/verification of complex ASICs / FPGAs.
Experience with Atlassian tool suite - JIRA, Stash, Bamboo.
Familiar with version control tool Git/Gerrit, SVN.
Excellent communication skills.
Ability to work independently.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:&#160;

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>WA</job_state>
    <job_city>Redmond</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>119123705</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Harness Design Engineer (Dragon)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexharness-design-engineer-dragon2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
HARNESS DESIGN ENGINEER (DRAGON)
As a Harness Design Engineer, you will be responsible for all wire harnesses within our Dragon capsules. You will own the designs from concept and component selection, through to production, qualification, and vehicle integration. This exciting multi-disciplinary role will give you unparalleled exposure to Dragon systems, where your creativity and relentless commitment to quality will be key components to building the safest and most reliable space vehicles. Our fundamental goal is to allow humanity to explore the stars; with it comes extreme responsibility to ensure the safety of the crew and payload. Are you up for the challenge?
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Develop the electro-mechanical design of wire harnesses within our family of Dragon capsules
Meet with multi-disciplinary stakeholders to gather harness design objectives and requirements&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;
Develop harness design solutions within a 3D NX CAD environment and manage technical trade studies to meet stakeholder objectives, as well as adhere to internal design standards and requirements
Generate electrical schematics to support both flight and qualification designs
Own vehicle-level harnessing mechanical assemblies and drive to closure all systems integration trades related to those assemblies
Perform analysis and physical testing (both mechanical and electrical) of harnessing with respect to thermal, loads, vibration, and shock to ensure full qualification for flight
Document and communicate the design, analysis and testing results thoroughly and clearly via design reviews
Create and release appropriate harnessing manufacturing documentation and drawings&#160;on-schedule
Interface with harness production and integration teams to ensure final harness designs can be produced and installed in accordance with overall project goals
Perform R&amp;D investigations and trade studies to push wire harness design to new boundaries in terms of mass and cost savings

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in an engineering discipline
2+ years of experience with electro-mechanical wire harness design

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Master&#8217;s degree or PhD in an engineering discipline
Proficiency with Siemens NX and Teamcenter
Experience with wire harness design, wire harness installations drawings and formboard creation, wiring diagrams, 3D modeling of complex top-level assemblies, 3D modeling and analysis of avionics enclosures and secondary structures
Wire harness component selection and qualification experience
General wire harness analysis, testing and qualification experience
Strong team working skills, with a proven ability to effectively interact and collaborate with other engineering disciplines, and excellent attention to detail
Capability to solve complex design problems to tight schedules with minimal supervision
Passion for advancing the commercial space industry and space exploration, with a strong desire to revolutionize wire harness design
Ability to work in a fast-paced, autonomously-driven, and demanding start-up atmosphere
Excellent communication skills both written and verbal
Strong sense of personal accountability and drive to succeed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1227179609</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>RF and Modem Integration Engineer</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexrf-and-modem-integration-engineer2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
RF AND MODEM INTEGRATION ENGINEER&#160;
As a member of the integration/test team, this position will play a critical role for integrating, testing and evaluating the functional performance, reliability and robustness of a complex satellite communication network. You will integrate the communication system components on satellite and ground station. You will explore, assess, track, and report performance status to project leaders.&#160; You will implement tools to conduct, track and improve testing processes and effectiveness. You will ensure that satellites and ground network provide the best possible communications system performance while also ensuring compliance with our operating licenses.
RESPONSIBILITIES:&#160;

Integrate and test satellite and ground broadband communications system components.
Analyze and implement RF and modem components supporting satellites and ground stations.
Design and deploy RF converters, integration and test equipment, auxiliary and ancillary equipment in support of integration lab and field testing.
Develop link budgets and cascades for analyzing performance expectations based on fielded/implemented designs.
Investigate discrepancies between expected and actual link performance through the analysis of operational data.
Provide expertise in performance verification of modem system performance parameters.
Understand and maintain regulatory requirements for satellite systems on a country basis.
Development of integration/test scripts.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:&#160;

Bachelor's degree in electrical engineering or computer engineering.&#160;
Experience with RF and radio design and communication.&#160;

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:&#160;

Master's degree in electrical engineering with emphasis in RF or radio communication.
5+ years of work experience.
Previous experience in characterizing radio performance in Ku-band and Ka-bands.
Previous experience in integrating advanced ground based and space based antennas.
Communications systems design, or integration and test experience in Wi-Fi, cellular or satellite systems.
Understanding of RF passive components such as hybrid couplers, Wilkinson dividers, waveguide, circulators, and directional couplers.
Knowledge of digital communication systems, single and multi-carrier techniques and modulation types such as BPSK, QPSK, QAM, PCM/FM, APSK, SC-FDMA, OFDM and OFDMA.
Experience in multiple access communication systems such as TDMA, CDMA and FDMA.
Understanding of channel coding such as LDPC, turbo codes, Reed-Solomon or convolutional codes.
Understanding of communication theory with emphasis on modulation, bit error rate, block error rate.
Understanding of RF concepts such as AGC, noise figure, power amplifier, phase noise, PLL, oscillators/mixers.
Experience in modeling RF and channel impairments such as multipath, phase noise, group delay, fading and nonlinear distortion.
Python and/or LabVIEW programming experience for test automation.
Experience in MATLAB, Python, C++ or equivalent tools for modeling and analyzing RF systems.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:&#160;

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here.&#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>WA</job_state>
    <job_city>Redmond</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>35096766</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1111801696</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3887085283</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1296656504</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1319796598</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>296913936</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Quality Inspector, CMM/Visual (Valve Factory)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexquality-inspector-cmmvisual-valve-factory2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
QUALITY INSPECTOR, CMM/VISUAL (VALVE FACTORY)
Our quality inspectors are responsible for being the last line of defense in assuring mission success. You will perform in-process inspections and verify that all key performance and design characteristics are met or exceeded during launch preparation and recovered booster processing. You will be working hands on with the most cutting edge rocket technology currently available and will be part of history. This position will be supporting the quality inspection team at the SpaceX valve factory, which is responsible for the most critical components of our Dragon and Falcon programs.
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Dimensional Inspection

Surface plate work/inspection
Inspect supplied product according to the applicable drawing and or work order specifications to verify that it conforms to all design requirements
Perform repetitive inspection following standardized methods
In-Process Inspection: visual and/or dimensional inspection of precision machined and sheet metal parts
Document production non-conformances in accordance with prescribed procedures and processes as required
Work in a cross functional environment utilizing PC-DMIS programming skills as applied to an Articulating Romer ARM and CMMs
Create, maintain and verify CMM programs used for the measurements of manufactured and supplied parts
Performs documentation review and verification of certifications, specifications, and conformance to design and specification requirements


Visual Inspection

Perform in process and final end to end inspections on flight hardware
Document production and test anomalies in accordance with prescribed procedures and process as required
Communicate and help resolve quality related issues as they relate to the site and other SpaceX locations i.e. launch site, production, and test sites
Process non-conforming product and assist engineering in root cause analysis and corrective actio
Routinely observe technical operations and offer guidance and/or serve as an additional technical resource
Determine manufacturing compliance to NASA and customer, as well as internal, specifications to meet launch and mission requirements
Perform other related duties, as assigned, for the purpose of ensuring an efficient and effective work environment



BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
3+ years of experience in precision mechanical inspection using PC-DMIS software
2+ years of inspection experience in an aerospace environment

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

CMM programming experience with PC-DMIS software
CMM programming experience with Modus software
Knowledge of quality assurance principles, methods, and processes
Strong knowledge and experience in aerospace standards
Intermediate level skill with Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint, Word, Outlook)
Intermediate level skill with Windows operating systems
ISO 9001 / AS9100 experience
NC inspection experience with PC-DMIS NC/ CAPPS NC
Romer Arm experience with Verisurf/ PCDMIS software
Solid computer skills in Microsoft Word, Outlook and Excel
DCC (Direct Computer Control) experience
Statistical process controls experience a plus
Ability to detect design and drawing flaws
Ability to read and interpret engineering drawings and specification using ASME Y14.5. GD&amp;T and skillful use of metrology tools and gauges

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be able to lift up to 25lbs. unassisted
Must be able to work all shift hours, overtime and weekends as needed
Acute attention to detail and critical thinking
Possess a positive attitude and be willing to assist anyone at any time

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX's Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>637651967</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>725344171</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Mechanical Facilities Technician</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmechanical-facilities-technician2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
FACILITIES MECHANICAL TECHNICIAN
Facilities mechanical technicians work in a fast paced environment, where the extraordinary becomes the everyday. The ideal candidate will be involved in all aspects facilities operations and maintenance, including new construction and renovation of existing facilities. Cape facilities delivers excellent service and products to our customers. Qualified candidates will have excellent communication and team building skills.&#160; Candidates will be responsible for operational and design feedback for maintaining and improving all systems at our facilities.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Maintain and repair facilities systems utilizing mechanical, plumbing, and carpentry skills
Troubleshoot, diagnose and repair equipment associated with: facility plumbing, doors, tile and carpeted floors, suspended ceilings, vacuum and air systems
Maintain and repair building structural systems and roofs
Collaborate with engineers and managers to maintain systems in peak operating condition
Follow all regulations and appropriate SpaceX procedures including quality and safety policies
Develop novel methods to streamline processes to increase reliability of internal processes

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High School Diploma or GED
5+ years mechanical and or construction tradesman experience

PREFERRED REQUIREMENTS:

Detail oriented, organized, and a high sense of urgency
Ability to accept directional changes in fast paced environment
Ability to lift 50 lbs., stand for extended periods, climb, bend, push and pull
Open to working extended shift hours, including overtime, and weekends as needed
Work routinely performed in extreme outdoor environments &#8211; heat, cold, rain
Ability to write detailed reports using basic functions of MS Outlook, MS Excel and PC computers
Proven safety record of safe work practices
Excellent attitude within a team setting

ITAR Requirements:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217; s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>FL</job_state>
    <job_city>Cape Canaveral</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3385718326</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Accounts Payable Specialist</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexaccounts-payable-specialist2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
ACCOUNTS PAYABLE SPECIALIST&#160;RESPONSIBILITIES:

Function in a high volume accounts payable (AP) environment, meeting regular transaction targets
Process and match invoices to purchase orders and resolve any discrepancies
Review invoices for appropriate documentation and approval prior to payment
Respond to questions from vendors and internal departments in a timely manner
Reconcile vendor statements, research, and correct discrepancies
Process expense reports
Assist in maintaining various Excel reports as needed at intermediate level
Import and export databases and files
Print, organize, and mail checks
Maintain files and documentation thoroughly and accurately, in accordance with company policy and accepted accounting practices
Perform other related duties and special projects as assigned

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

2 years of accounts payable, finance, or operations experience
Strong motivation for automation and process improvement
General knowledge of generally accepted accounting principles (GAAP)
Proficient computer skills, including Excel and Microsoft Dynamics AX or other ERP Software
SQL experience
Good written and oral communication skills
Ability to work independently and with a team in a fast-paced and high volume environment with emphasis on accuracy and timeliness
Possess strong organizational and time management skills
Ability to interact with employees and vendors in a professional manner

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR&#160;here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3886552249</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3915352513</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Stock Plan Administrator</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexstock-plan-administrator2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
STOCK PLAN ADMINISTRATOR 
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Administer&#160;SpaceX&#8217;s&#160;equity-based incentive compensation including stock options, restricted stock units&#160;(RSU&#8217;S),&#160;employee stock purchase plan (ESPP),&#160;and other equity-based incentive compensation tools
Process option grants, exercises and cancellations,&#160;restricted&#160;stock unit grants and releases and ESPP purchases
Maintain the online equity administration portal and ensure accuracy at all times
Prepare equity-related communications and online training materials
Conduct participant training sessions on equity compensation and use of the online portal
Assist in calculation of stock based compensation expense
Assist with external audits by providing supporting records and documentation
Partner with Payroll to prepare and distribute year-end statements of taxable income, W-2 and 1099-B income calculations and tax filings related to equity transactions
Provide superior customer service to equity plan participants of all levels

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

2+ years of experience in stock plan administration

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Bachelors&#8217; degree in business, finance, accounting, economics, mathematics, or a similar field
Experience with Solium Shareworks
Highly Proficient with Microsoft Office (e.g., Word, Excel and PowerPoint)
Excellent written and oral communication skills
Strong attention to detail and accuracy
Familiarity with FAS 123(R) (ASC 718) and tax implications of equity compensation
CEP certification

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Willing to travel 10% of the time, if needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1880974677</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Dining Room Attendant</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexdining-room-attendant2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
DINING ROOM ATTENDANT
This is a leadership position for an individual ready to steer a team to success in a fast paced restaurant and catering environment. They will support the mission by providing excellent customer service and quality food options that boost morale and productivity within SpaceX.
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Assist in the organization and cleanliness of all on-site dining areas
Coordinate and execute catering requests for meetings
Oversee maintenance of all beverage stations, including inventory and restocking supplies
Act as point of contact for vendors and technicians
Adjust staffing according to the days situation at hand
Exercise strong customer service and communication skills

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma, GED, or a minimum of 6 months of work experience

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

A valid ServSafe or state food handler&#8217;s card
Ability to work under pressure and take initiative in a fast paced environment
Comfortable working in high volume output environment
Demonstrated excellence in guest service skills: reliable, consistent, informative, and pleasant
Able to withstand frequent bending, stooping, and lifting of objects up to 25 lbs.
Strong knowledge of styles of service such as casual dining, fine dining, buffet, ala carte, etc.
Manager edition of the ServSafe certification
Self-motivated and works well with others
Strong understanding of food safety and sanitation practices
Effective interpersonal and oral communication skills

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Ability to work in a continuously-standing position for four or more hours
Physically capable of performing manual labor tasks (lifting up to 25 lbs.)
Ability to work all shifts and available for overtime and weekends as needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>TX</job_state>
    <job_city>McGregor</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1625131913</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Food Services Specialist</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexfood-services-specialist2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
FOOD SERVICES SPECIALIST
As a Food Services Specialist at SpaceX, This is an entry level position for an individual that enjoys a fast paced, changing environment. They must be comfortable in both Front of House and Back of House roles, and flexible enough to switch from one to the other throughout the day according to specification by leadership. A high level of communication is necessary in this role. Specific daily tasks may change on short notice according to staffing and business needs and include, but are not limited to the following: food preparation, meal delivery, serving guests, maintaining the cleanliness of dining spaces, and stocking or ordering product. This individual should be cross-trained in more than one specific role so that they are able to fill in at a moment&#8217;s notice. The Food Services Specialist position supports the mission by providing excellent customer service, quality food and beverage options, and boosting morale and productivity within SpaceX.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Fill in for different FOH/BOH roles according to the day&#8217;s staffing situation
Assist in the organization and cleanliness of all on-site dining areas
Coordinate and execute catering requests for meetings
Oversee maintenance of all beverage stations, including inventory and restocking supplies
Assist with food preparation according to SpaceX quality and sanitation standards
Support proper product rotation and delivery
Follow stocking route, track inventory, and place orders for product as needed
Act as point of contact for vendors and technicians
Exercise strong customer service and communication skills
Meet the time and quality standards set by supervisor for any additional assignments

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
At least 2yrs experience in food preparation or customer service

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

A valid ServSafe or state food handler&#8217;s card
Ability to work under pressure and take initiative in a fast paced environment
Comfortable working in high volume output environment
Demonstrated excellence in guest service skills: reliable, consistent, informative, and pleasant
Strong knowledge of styles of service such as casual dining, fine dining, buffet, ala carte, etc.
Self-motivated and works well with others
Competent in Microsoft Office
Strong understanding of food safety and sanitation practices
Effective interpersonal and oral communication skills

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Ability to work in a continuously-standing position for four or more hours
Physically capable of performing manual labor tasks (lifting up to 25 lbs.)
Ability to work all shifts and available for overtime and weekends as needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>WA</job_state>
    <job_city>Redmond</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1980568073</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Porter</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexporter2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
PORTER
As a Porter at SpaceX, you will be interacting with our guests (employees), fellow staff members, and management staff in our private restaurant in a polite courteous manner. You will also help with restocking supplies and other duties assigned by kitchen management.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Demonstrate sanitation and food safety practices consistently
Help evaluate receiving spaces to ensure a safe and secure environment
Complete daily, weekly, and monthly tasks timely and accurately
Follow company safety standards at all times and looks out for the safety of other team members and guests
Coordinate job duties around other opening team members to help ensure efficient preparation for opening
Put food order away accurately, rotate stock in cooler, freezer, and dry storage area using the first in-first out (FIFO) method while monitoring shelf life and code dates
Maintain a basic working knowledge of the operation of all the equipment in the restaurant
Complete other miscellaneous tasks as assigned by the manager on duty

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:1 year of either restaurant experience, warehouse experience, and/or customer service experience

High school Diploma or GED

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Restaurant experience
Porter experience
Inventory experience
Self-motivated and works well with others
Current and valid CA Food Handler&#8217;s Card or equivalent

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Ability to carry large heavy items unassisted such as large packages, dishes in tubs, or trays (up to 50lbs.)
Ability to stand for long periods of time &#8211; up to 8-10 hours a day
Willingness to work all shifts and available for overtime and weekends as needed
Frequent bending, stooping, and lifting of objects

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>FL</job_state>
    <job_city>Cape Canaveral</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3271796504</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>586550876</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1940925915</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>IT Services Technician II &#8211; Temporary Position</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexit-services-technician-ii-temporary-position2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
IT Services Technician II &#8211; Temporary Position &#160;
The launch and mission IT team is responsible for supporting all networks and systems associated with SpaceX launch, mission, and recovery operations globally.&#160; This position will be responsible for supporting launch and mission operations administrators and engineers at our development site in Brownsville, TX.
Responsibilities:

Provide 1st and 2nd tier support to SpaceX employees who require assistance with their information technology resources.
Install and configure computers, telephones, and other common technology/devices for new and existing SpaceX employees.
Provide after-hours or weekend support when necessary to perform high-risk or planned downtime of SpaceX IT systems for upgrades and maintenance.
Support SpaceX with the regular maintenance of monitoring, backup, and infrastructure systems.
Provide &#8216;remote hands&#8217; support for SpaceX systems administrators as needed to include racking of servers, network devices, and rack-mountable power systems.

Position Details:
This is a&#160;TEMPORARY&#160;position with SpaceX, for the length of time as stated, and is subject to change with minimal notice as business needs dictate.

LENGTH OF POSITION: 12 months; through May 2019
LOCATION: Brownsville, TX

Basic Qualifications:

3+ years&#8217; work experience building, deploying and troubleshooting computer systems.
Experience working within an enterprise environment.
Experience troubleshooting hardware, printers, and software, Microsoft technologies including Windows 7, Windows Server, and Microsoft Office.
Experience supporting and troubleshooting network equipment and IP networks.
Enterprise experience working with system imaging and configuration management systems, such as Microsoft Systems Center Configuration Manager (SCCM).
Experience racking and stacking servers.

Preferred Skills and Experience:

Associate&#8217;s or bachelor&#8217;s degree in computer science or technical field.
A+, Network+, MCSE, and other technical certifications.
Working knowledge of audio visual equipment.
Ability to take on higher-level strategic projects when tactical projects stall. Areas can include network administration, systems administration, high-performance computing, information security, etc.
Ability to write instructional documentation and convey highly technical ideas in simple terms.
Ability to address and resolve information technology issues promptly, effectively and independently.
Motivated self-starter personality, able to work independently while maintaining patience with the constant interruptions of needy coworkers.
Comfortable working with mission critical and sensitive systems, with a sense of urgency appropriate to the responsibilities.

Additional Requirements:

Must be physically fit enough to regularly lift up to 30 lbs. for duties such as delivering computers, unpacking and rack-mounting equipment, etc.
Must be comfortable working at heights up to 110 meters with appropriate safety equipment.
Some travel, including air travel and extended time at sea, is required for operational and training purposes.

ITAR Requirements:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
&#160;
&#160;
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>TX</job_state>
    <job_city>Brownsville</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3550124925</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3616284587</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3584909167</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Civil Engineer &#8211; Construction Management</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexcivil-engineer-construction-management2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
CIVIL ENGINEER &#8211; CONSTRUCTION MANAGEMENT
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Manage the civil and structural aspects of construction projects
Manage project budgets, schedules, and general project controls
Interact with contractors, fabricators, owners, and clients
Provide direct on-site engineering inspections and field observations
Resolve design and construction conflicts in the field in real time
Perform structural design and analysis calculations for structural steel and concrete

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor's degree in civil engineering, structural engineering, or mechanical engineering
2+ years of professional experience in civil and/or structural engineering design, analysis, and drafting
2+ years of professional experience in civil, structural, or mechanical field engineering and project management

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Professional Engineering (PE) license
Knowledge of American Institute of&#160; Steel Construction (AISC) steel manual, American Concrete Institute (ACI) code 318, American Society of Civil Engineers (ASCE) 7, and &#160;International Building Code (IBC)
Experience with AutoCAD or similar design software
Knowledge of processes of governing permitting agencies such as building departments and/or environmental agencies
Understanding of other disciplines such as: mechanical, electrical, piping, geotechnical, and surveying
Experience with project management of major construction projects including cost, schedule, and subcontractor management
Experience reading, reviewing, and approving shop and fabrication drawings, blueprints, and technical manuals
Experience with at least three of the following project delivery phases: 1) conceptual layout and high level trade studies &#160;2) detailed engineering design and development &#160;3) request for proposals/quotes &amp; contract issues&#160; 4) supervision of construction to completion &#160;5) work punch lists and certificate of occupancy (CO) with building official
Strong written and verbal communication skills

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be willing to travel
Ability to pass Air Force background checks for Cape Canaveral, FL and Vandenberg, CA sites

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>FL</job_state>
    <job_city>Cape Canaveral</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3101457583</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>277131851</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Launch Communications Engineer</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexlaunch-communications-engineer2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
LAUNCH COMMUNICATIONS ENGINEER
The Launch Communications group supports launch site operations with operational voice, mission-critical video, vehicle and payload interface RF systems, site communications infrastructure, and real-time operations. Engineers and specialists on our communications team provide system design and development, critical performance evaluation, customer interface systems, and upgrades that enable safe and successful launches and spacecraft support.&#160;
RESPONSIBILITIES

Design, construct, and maintain:

Operational voice (wired and wireless) intercom systems
Site-wide Motorola two-way radio systems
Video cameras, video distribution systems, and video control applications
High speed imaging systems
Timing systems (GPS timing receivers, IRIG-B and CS-5 count distribution)
Public address systems
Satellite RF re-radiation systems to customer ground equipment
Satellite ground stations


Perform trade studies to define communication system requirements and optimizations
Assist with proposals and specification development related to launch site facility-to-range and launch vehicle-to-ground communication systems
Provide support in the assessment, specification development and testing of radio frequency systems
Work in the field, performing hands-on designing and troubleshooting

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS

At least 2 years of project or industry experience with communications systems, controls, and/or RF
At least 1 year of project or industry experience designing, implementing and testing system-level architectures

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in electrical engineering, aerospace engineering, or other applicable engineering disciplines
Able to perform field work, able to work with hands, and have real-world knowledge of working with tools and test equipment
Experience performing RF link analysis for launch vehicle and satellite systems
Experience in the installation and operation of RF communication systems
Experience with IP and HD-SDI Video cameras and infrastructure
Experience with wired and wireless voice intercom communication systems
Knowledge of C++, Python, LabVIEW, MATLAB, and Linux OS
Experience with serial data communications systems including acquisition, storage, processing, transport and display -- including TCP/IP, EIA 530, and PCM/FM
Experience with configuration and operation of TCP/IP based communication equipment&#160;
Basic familiarity with electronics labs and environments
Demonstrated excellence in leadership, communications, and briefing skills, with an ability to interface with key stakeholders
Familiarity with NASA telemetry standards, TDRS SNUG, Federal Communications Commission (FCC regulations, and Range Commanders Council (RCC) Inter Range Instrumentation Group (IRIG) standards
Must be able to work well in an integrated collaborative team environment including daily interactions with technicians, engineers, and managers
Able to run with a project from early design stage to implementation and testing
Self-motivated and directed with keen attention to detail

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS

Must pass background checks at Cape Canaveral Air Force Base and Vandenberg Air Force Base
Must be willing to travel (approximately 10%) to other launch sites as necessary
Must be willing to work long hours and weekends when necessary to support launch and critical project timelines, flexibility required
Must be able to lift a minimum of 35 lbs. unassisted
Lifting, standing, climbing, bending, grasping, sitting, pulling, pushing, stooping, stretching, and carrying are generally required to perform the functions of this position

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>FL</job_state>
    <job_city>Cape Canaveral</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3685773382</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Manager, Launch Communications (Ground Segment)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmanager-launch-communications-ground-segment2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.
MANAGER, LAUNCH COMMUNICATIONS (GROUND SEGMENT)
The launch communications group supports busy launch site operations with operational voice, mission critical video, vehicle and payload interface RF systems, site communications infrastructure, and real time operations. This position would manage multiple teams of engineers and technicians at SpaceX launch sites.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Manage teams of engineers, specialists, and technicians to develop and maintain mission critical communication systems
Effectively assign tasks, evaluate task progress, provide corrective feedback,&#160;and ensure task completion on time and within established budget
Assist in the development of highly reliable and automated operational interfaces for a variety of both commercial and SpaceX built hardware
Responsible for full project life-cycle management of communication systems and commercial or custom built hardware
Perform real-time operations according to timeline, procedures and flight rules
Develop requirements, drive schedule, delegate actions, and provide oversight on all phases of a project including design, implementation and support, and troubleshooting of the mission-critical communication systems
Own asset inventory, configuration management, capacity management, performance management, resource optimization, and security of all launch communication systems
Drive consistent standardized solutions across SpaceX for all launch communications hardware, software, configurations, and processes
Manage site maintenance, upgrades, and changes to existing systems for flawless operation
Interact with internal customers to provide solutions and resolve problems in a timely and proactive manner
Interface with external partners (private and government) to define hardware and software interfaces for voice, video, data, and RF communications

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree
5+ years of professional experience with communication systems
2+ years of professional experience in a team or project leadership capacity

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in electrical engineering, management, or other related discipline
Demonstrated excellence in team leadership, communications and briefing skills, task management
Demonstrated experience with capabilities based analysis, system architecture development, requirements analysis and traceability, analysis of alternatives, interoperability, and risk management
Must be able to work well in an integrated collaborative team environment including daily interactions with technicians, engineers, and managers
Telecommunication infrastructure management experience - fiber optic and cable plant
Experience in the installation and operation of RF communication systems
Experience with IP and HD-SDI video cameras and infrastructure
Ability to translate specifications and functional descriptions into design specifications and detailed build documentation
Experience with project management of remote systems and teams

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Ability to travel frequently (20% or more) as required to common destinations including Hawthorne, CA; McGregor and Brownsville, TX; Vandenberg, CA; Seattle, WA as well as any of the SpaceX national or international ground station sites. Direct reports will be located at three different launch sites (majority of team will be located in Florida)
Must pass Air Force background checks for Cape Canaveral and Vandenberg

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR&#160;here.&#160;&#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation,&#160;gender identity,&#160;marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or&#160;applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources&#160;Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>FL</job_state>
    <job_city>Cape Canaveral</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2438844274</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4157141197</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1956841983</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3387418668</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1957228310</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1610840684</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>277714339</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2385986609</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3963749737</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3930849657</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1679064244</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Manufacturing Engineer (Falcon Tank Manufacturing)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmanufacturing-engineer-falcon-tank-manufacturing2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.&#160;MANUFACTURING ENGINEER (FALCON TANK MANUFACTURING)
RESPONSIBILITIES:&#160;

Own the launch vehicle build process for Falcon 9 and Falcon Heavy Primary Structure
Responsible for developing and refining new processes to increase vehicle reliability and reduce cost
Influence and lead cross-functional teams with design for manufacturability to improve manufacturing processes
Own design, analysis, and integration of first and second stage assembly to resolve off-nominal non-conformance and develop sustainable repair procedures
Resolve recurring manufacturing discrepancies and interface with quality team to implement corrective actions
Find and eliminate process waste, streamline production processes, and enable continuous improvement
Identify, plan, and execute lean manufacturing projects to meet volume production demand and reduce cost
Interface with Production technician and leadership teams on a daily basis

&#160;BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in mechanical, materials, or aerospace engineering or engineering physics
Minimum 1 year of manufacturing experience in integration roles such as: fabrication, assembly, test, or repair
2+ years of collegiate extracurricular engineering project experience, such as Formula SAE, Baja SAE, design build fly team, OR 2+ years of industry product design/development experience

&#160;PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Master's degree in mechanical/chemical/aerospace engineering
Experience with large-scale structures integration or manufacturing processes (prefer aerospace or equivalent)
Expertise in design for manufacturability and design for assembly, successfully taking products through development, testing, and production
Experience with hardware test methodologies including structural testing and nondestructive evaluation (NDE)
Experience navigating and modifying large assemblies in CAD (NX &amp; Teamcenter is a plus)
Experience in a production environment within the aerospace industry

&#160;ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

This is a hands-on position that may require standing for up to 4 hours a day and working directly with hardware on the floor
Must be comfortable stooping, bending, standing, and entering a confined space
Position may require long hours and weekend work

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

&#160;SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
&#160;Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
&#160;
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>456000634</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Manufacturing Engineer - Development &amp; Tooling</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmanufacturing-engineer-development-tooling2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
MANUFACTURING ENGINEER &#8211; DEVELOPMENT &amp; TOOLING
Join our fast paced, R&amp;D-focused group that supports the development, testing, automation and tooling for the Starlink constellation.&#160; Our Manufacturing Engineers will work closely with designers, technicians, and vendors to support procurement, machining, fabrication, assembly, testing, and commissioning.
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Manage the build and delivery of tooling and testing equipment utilizing both internal fabrication resources and external supplier bases.
Provide fabrication project management for up to 40 projects simultaneously to ensure schedule and cost adherence, starting in the design phase of a project and ending upon successful implementation of the hardware.
Create cost and schedule estimates for piece parts and assemblies.
Work with designers to optimize manufacturability.
Interpret technical documents (2D drawings) from engineering and envision potential sequence and methods of manufacture.
Create, revise, and maintain planning and procurement documents to produce parts and components which conform to design configuration and specifications.
Obtain and negotiate proposals from an established supplier base.
Prepare and execute purchase order contracts with suppliers. Including machined components, weldments, heat-treating and plating.
Monitor status of supplier work and ensure timely delivery of goods and services.
Resolve manufacturing, supplier quality, and invoice issues.
Support the overall sourcing strategies, negotiations and documenting of contracts and agreements.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor's degree in an engineering discipline.
Minimum of 2 years of experience in a manufacturing or construction environment.

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

5+ years project management experience executing custom fabrication and equipment.
Experience in cost projections and project scheduling.
Experience in machining, welding, assembly, rigging, and heavy equipment.
Experience in a supply chain role involving supplier relations and contracts.
Experience using 2D/3D CAD programing, NX and AutoCAD a plus.
Practical Experience with GD&amp;T.
Engineering design fundamentals including stress analysis and hand calculations.
Experience with SQL and understanding of Statistical Methods.

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be open to working long hours and weekends as needed.
Ability to travel to vendors (up to 10%-20%).

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>WA</job_state>
    <job_city>Redmond</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>90215449</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4204992556</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>431799321</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>222057891</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3356055806</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2419145111</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>38862597</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1861564929</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Production Control Scheduler (Dragon Spacecraft)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexproduction-control-scheduler-dragon-spacecraft2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
PRODUCTION CONTROL SCHEDULER (DRAGON SPACECRAFT)
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Provide tactical scheduling and strategic long range planning expertise to our Dragon production teams
Coordinate, review, plan and schedule input from engineering, propulsion, avionics, manufacturing, suppliers, and business development to develop and maintain Integrated Master Plans (IMP) and Integrated Master Schedules (IMS) for programs using Microsoft Project or applicable software as required
Ensures MRP dates align with current vehicle products
Utilize our Factory Scheduler application and other applicable tools to ensure work is scheduled and prioritized accurately and efficiently, and resources allocated appropriately
Prepare daily work schedules, track work progress, update project critical path schedules, and advise leadership of needed adjustments to daily work activities
Perform schedule baseline change control, collection and tracking performance, critical path analysis and variance analysis as required
Ensure fixture, tooling, and test equipment requirements are properly scheduled to facilitate an efficient production process

Production Process Support:

Schedule production, operations planning, and engineering support to eliminate obstacles and deliver product on time
Remain abreast and knowledgeable regarding applicable facilities and manpower
Coordinate team needs with any support organizations applicable
Lead efforts to uncover root-cause and develop permanent resolution on issues found during product builds as required
Identify and support improvement opportunities for product yield, quality, safety, cost and team efficiency
Develop and Support efforts to streamline assigned value streams and automate production processes as applicable

Reporting:

Organize and communicate the daily priorities to production coordinators, team leads and supervisors as required
Provide daily visibility, weekly status, and monthly reviews on schedule performance
Develop and analyze metrics that tie production to enterprise goals as required
Create and use tools using queries and Excel to highlight shortages and determine schedule risks

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
5 years of manufacturing scheduling experience

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

2 years of scheduling experience with MS Project or similar scheduling software
4 years of practical experience with ERP/MRP systems in a production environment
Familiarity with lean principles, six sigma and Kaizan
Project management professional certification
Experience writing queries with SQL

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be available for all shifts, overtime, and weekends as needed
Must be able to lift 25 lbs unassisted

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:


To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR&#160;here.


SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1735425990</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1774399224</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Lead Avionics Quality Inspector</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexlead-avionics-quality-inspector2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
Lead Avionics Quality Inspector
The Avionics Production Quality Assurance team is looking for a Lead Inspector to provide technical leadership to our teams of quality inspectors in the production areas for Electo-Mechanical Assembly, PCBA (SMT) Assembly, Space Simulations Test Lab and Battery Assembly.
Responsibilities:

Provide leadership to production inspection team while enhancing workflow and efficiency to improve product yield and cost of quality.
Conduct thorough reviews of work instructions, make improvement recommendations to enhance efficiency &amp; reliability, and follow-through action plans to execution.
Ensure that inspection systems, processes and equipment reliably deliver quality products that meet all requirements and drive execution of production schedule.
Manage all aspects of nonconforming product procedures &#8211; identify and contain risk material, drive root-cause investigation, disposition affected product with engineering rationale, implement corrective and preventive actions, and maintain complete quality records.&#160;

Basic Qualifications:

A minimum of 3 years of Quality Assurance experience in electronic and mechanical assembly.
A minimum of 3 years of experience with the control of nonconforming hardware, failure/root cause analysis, corrective and preventive action processes.

Preferred Skills and Experience:

Associate&#8217;s degree in quality or manufacturing.
Good communication skills and the ability to articulate aerospace hardware and systems problems to technical professionals to initiate resolutions.
Experience inspecting solder, crimping, conformal coating, staking, and surface mounted devices accordance with NASA 8739 and/or IPC-J-STD-001, IPC-A-610 standards.
Wire harness experience in accordance with NASA-STD-8739.3 and 8739.4 and/or IPC-A-620 standards.
Knowledge of ISO 9001 / AS9100 Quality Management Systems.
Excellent people management skills and technical know-how to provide hands-on coaching and mentoring.
Proficient with computers, the ability to use MS Office, shop floor management software (ERP) as well as SpaceX proprietary programs and systems.
Must be a self-starter and highly motivated and able to work in a fast paced, high demand environment.
Experience coding SQL scripts to data mine quality issues and product actionable information a plus.

Additional Requirements:

Must be willing to work all shifts, overtime, and weekends as needed.
Must be able to lift a minimum of 25 lbs. unassisted.
Able to travel for short and extended trips as needed. Up to 10% travel.
Ability to pass Air Force background checks for Cape Canaveral and Vandenberg.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2001618775</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Quality Inspector (Composites and Integration)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexquality-inspector-composites-and-integration2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.
QUALITY INSPECTOR (COMPOSITE STRUCTURES AND INTEGRATION)
Responsibilities:

Provide detailed in-process inspections on launch vehicle composite components, using detailed drawings, CAD models, and established processes to verify conformance to manufacturing and design requirements.
Ensure company policies and procedures are complied with for the receiving and storage of composite raw materials.
Document production non-conformances in accordance with prescribed procedures and processes as required.
Support Quality Management System policies and procedure documentation, assess compliance to company and industry standards, initiate and lead continual improvement and Lean Manufacturing initiatives.
Support the Material Review Board (MRB) process by documenting and managing non-conformances.

Basic Qualifications:

A minimum of 2 years of experience in composite component fabrication OR other manufacturing environment.
2 years of experience with AS 9100, ISO 9001, ISO/TS 16949, ISO 13485, or similar Quality Management System.
2 years of experience reading and interpreting design drawings and CAD models.

Preferred Skills and Experience:

Bachelor's degree or Associate's degree in a technical or engineering field or 5+ years of experience in a Quality, Inspection, or Manufacturing role.
A&amp;P license.
Strong understanding of composite layup laser alignment and composite ply cutting systems.
Ability to read and interpret cure reports vendor supplied conformance certifications.
Practical experience with GD&amp;T and skillful use of metrology tools and gauges.
Experience with Integration.
Experience working with, manufacturing enterprise resource systems, electronic databases, and paperless work instructions.
Working knowledge of Microsoft Office Suite.
Strong communication skills. Must be able to effectively communicate with engineering and production groups.
Must be self-motivated, proactive, and capable of managing priorities and tasks as delegated.
Strong understanding of safety programs and OSHA regulations and requirements.
Experience with AS 9100, ISO 9001, ISO/TS 16949, ISO 13485, or similar Quality Management System.

Additional Requirements:

Must be able to work all shifts, overtime and weekend hours, as needed.
Must be able to lift up to 25lbs. unassisted.
Must be able to stand for extended periods - 8 hours minimum.
Must be able to stoop, bend, crawl, and able to maneuver in tight spaces.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here.&#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1624358008</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Quality Inspector - Dragon Spacecraft 2nd Shift</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexquality-inspector-dragon-spacecraft-2nd-shift2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
QUALITY INSPECTOR &#8211; DRAGON SPACECRAFT 2ND SHIFT
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Provide detailed in-process inspections on Dragon spacecraft electrical and mechanical assemblies, using detailed drawings, CAD models, and established processes to verify conformance to design requirements.
Identify, document, and resolve production and test anomalies in accordance with prescribed procedures and pursue corrective action as required.
Communicate and help resolve quality related issues as they relate to the Dragon spacecraft integration department.
Document production non-conformances in accordance with prescribed procedures and processes as required.
Support Quality Management System policies and procedure documentation, assess compliance to company and industry standards, initiate and lead continual improvement and Lean Manufacturing initiatives.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

At least 3 years of practical experience in a launch vehicle/spacecraft hardware integration environment.
Experience with reading and interpreting design drawings and CAD models.

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

BS or AA in a technical or engineering field is preferred.
Experience working with spacecraft avionics installation and testing.
Experience working with propulsion systems and testing.
Experience working with Material Review Board and Root Cause/Corrective Action systems.
Self-motivated, proactive, and capable of managing priorities and tasks as delegated.
Wire harness experience in accordance with NASA-STD-8739.3 and 8739.4 and/or IPC-A-620 standards.
Experience with performing electronic testing and inspections using portable measuring devices.
Strong understanding of safety programs and OSHA regulations and requirements.
Practical experience working within Quality Management Systems (AS9100 and ISO 9001).

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be able to lift up to 25lbs. unassisted.
Must be able to stand for extended periods &#8211; 8 hours min.
Must be able to stoop, bend, crawl, and being able to maneuver in tight spaces.
Must be able to work all shift hours, able to work overtime and weekend as needed.
Must be able to travel for short trips as needed. Up to 10% travel.
Ability to pass Air Force background checks for Cape Canaveral and Vandenberg

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>45419069</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Receiving Inspector - 2nd shift</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexreceiving-inspector-2nd-shift2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars
RECEIVING&#160;INSPECTOR (2nd Shift)
Responsibilities:

Utilize inspection equipment such as micrometers, calipers and profilometer
Approve or reject items and document inspection results as required
Perform documentation review and verification of certifications, specifications, and conformance to design requirements
Communicate with internal customers and suppliers to resolve inspection discrepancies
Use electronic MRP system to route parts and components to proper departments&#160;
Maintain strict material handling practices in accordance with good practice and procedures
Verify all material received for conformity with accompanying paperwork, checking for damage, correct part numbers and quantity as required
Evaluate hazardous receipts/shipments and determine applicable methodology and packaging specifications
Coordinate internal receipt pickup and internal delivery service as required

Basic Qualifications:

High school diploma or GED
Minimum 1 year of receiving, precision, mechanical, or metrological inspection experience

Preferred Skills and Experience:

Forklift and other related inventory equipment experience
Experience within the aerospace, automotive, semiconductor, or electronic fields
Experience detecting design and drawing flaws
Ability to read and interpret engineering drawings and specifications using ASME Y14.5
Experience with GD&amp;T and use of metrology tools and gauges
Experience with Microsoft Word, Outlook and Excel

Additional Requirements:

Ability to lift 30 lbs. unassisted
Standing, climbing, bending, grasping, sitting, pulling, pushing, stooping, stretching, and carrying are a part of this role
Ability to work all required shift hours, including overtime and weekends as needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>WA</job_state>
    <job_city>Redmond</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3660803795</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Test Technician - Composites Structures</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacextest-technician-composites-structures2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
TEST TECHNICIAN &#8211; COMPOSITE STRUCTURES 
Test Technicians at SpaceX get to assemble, troubleshoot, repair, and perform regular maintenance and work on integrated rocket hardware, including fuel tanks and integrated stages, as well as supporting test equipment. These technicians enjoy working outside at the rocket development facility, on our robust test stands, supporting structural test operations first-hand, as well as in the hangar where stage integration takes place. Test Technicians enjoy witnessing the rumbling of rocket engines throughout the day.
&#160;RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Ensure all structural test stand related equipment/services are performed on time, safely, and in a professional manner.
Maintain, troubleshoot, and repair equipment and instrumentation as needed.
Fabricate and repair structural hardware and test equipment.
Collaborate with engineers to develop and document activities.
Operate and maintain hardware, high pressure systems and pumps, and other ancillary equipment including pneumatic components.
Develop novel ways site wide to streamline processes and increase the reliability of testing operations.
Obtain and maintain licenses, operator permits or certifications as required.
Perform a variety of related duties in support of structural test programs.
Maintain inventory of spare parts and equipment to repair or replace defective components.
Process work orders and maintenance tickets.
Prepare test articles and test stands and systems for test operations.

&#160;BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED.
Experience working with and troubleshooting mechanical systems. (professional work experience or personal experience will be considered)
Experience using power tools, hand tools, or heavy equipment.

&#160;PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Associates degree.
A&amp;P License.
Experience with hydraulic structural test equipment/services is a plus.
Experience with testing process and optimization of test processes.
Experience with high performance systems and optimization of these systems.
Experience in ground support equipment in aerospace industry preferred.
Some experience in the space exploration industry, aviation, military or other high-reliability operating environment.
Basic computer skills, including experience using MS Office suite.
Experience with crane operations.
Knowledge of different fittings such as NPT and A/N.
Ability to utilize power tools and hand tools as well as heavy equipment.
A demonstrated ability in reading/understanding technical manuals and reports.
Use of precision measuring instruments.
Communication skills for relaying data (verbally and in-writing) between other employees and customers.
Ability to work effectively in a team environment.
Be able to rapidly change roles/responsibilities while working in a high-paced, challenging work environment.

&#160;ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be able to lift up to 25lbs. unassisted.
Must be able to stand for extended periods &#8211; 8 hours minimum.
Must be able to stoop, bend, crawl, and able to maneuver in tight spaces.
Must be able to work all shift hours, able to work overtime and weekend as needed.
Must be able to travel for short and extended trips as needed. Up to 5% travel
Ability to pass Air Force background checks for Cape Canaveral and Vandenberg.

&#160;ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

&#160;SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
&#160;Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>729146735</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>5-Axis CNC Machinist - 2nd Shift</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacex5-axis-cnc-machinist-2nd-shift2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
5-AXIS CNC MACHINIST - 2ND SHIFT&#160;
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Responsible for setting up and operating a 5-axis CNC machine
Proficient at all types of drilling, tapping, and milling
Complete machining operations from blueprints, drawings and/or verbal instructions
Knowledge of complex, tight tolerance parts, and various materials

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
5+ years of experience setting up and operating 5-axis CNC machines

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Experience with Renishaw Inspection and probing software
Knowledge of Fanuc 31i controllers
Ability to read and work off of a blueprint

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Available for a 5 day shift that may include overtime as needed&#160;
Ability to lift a minimum of 50 lbs. unassisted
Ability to work overtime and 2nd&#160;shift hours as needed
Ability to stand for extended periods - 8 hours minimum
Ability to stoop, bend, crawl, and maneuver in tight spaces
Comfortable with repetitive movement, bending or twisting, and using hands to handle, control, or feel objects, tools or controls, and exposure to sounds and noise levels that are distracting

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3552310289</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1130250595</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2680143467</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1041103941</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2436121361</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Composites Technician</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexcomposites-technician2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.
COMPOSITES TECHNICIAN
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Trimming/finishing of composite and composite metallic assemblies
Assembly of structures including setup, bonding and fastener applications
Surface prep, using grit blast, hand abrade and power abrasion techniques
Laminate assemblies by determining proper placement of composite materials into molds
Prepare parts for bagging, including placement of bleeders, thermocouples, probes and vacuum connections
Vacuum bag processing, bonding, and oven/autoclave curing
Making basic layouts on parts or assemblies in order to establish reference points and to check dimensions using calipers, micrometers, precision scales and torque wrenches

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
Minimum of 2 years with layup, bonding or assembly of composites with at least 1 year of experience with composite tooling materials (prepreg, wet layup) OR completion of an Airframe and Powerplant Program (A&amp;P) from an&#160;accredited school

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Experience with reaming, honing and/or countersinking of uniform close tolerance holes in proper sequence while using the correct tool for the job (e.g., rivet gun and bucking bar, drill motor, power screwdriver, C-squeeze, ratchet wrench, nut runner)
Experience with Thermal Protection System (TPS) or Phenolic Impregnated Carbon Ablator (PICA)
Experience operating a ply cutting machine
Experience operating a laser projector to layout laminated assemblies
Experience reading and interpreting engineering drawings, an understanding for drawing symbols, flag notes and general notes
Ability to follow written and verbal instructions, read Travelers and SOPs (Standard Operating Procedures)
Attention to detail and accuracy while working within a fast-paced production environment

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Standing for long periods of time, climbing up and down ladders, bending, grasping, sitting, pulling, pushing, stooping, and stretching are generally required to perform the functions of this position
Must be able to lift and carry up to 25lbs. unassisted
Must be able to climb ladders and work in tight spaces
Must be willing to work all required shift hours, overtime and weekends as needed
Must be willing to travel up to 100% (within the Greater Los Angeles area)

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2226344993</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1810649924</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Electron Beam Welder</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexelectron-beam-welder2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
ELECTRON BEAM WELDER (MERLIN SUB-ASSEMBLY)
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Operation of CNC-controlled electron-beam (EB) welding machines including part set-up.
Development, maintenance and evaluation of weld schedules.
General machine maintenance and test.
EB welding on several types of metal including titanium, stainless steel, copper, C103, and inconel.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED.
Minimum of 5 years&#8217; experience in aerospace EB welding.
Experience in G-code programming and weld schedule development.

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE: 

Both high- and low-voltage machine experience.
Experience with both manual and robotic welding applications.
TIG welding experience.
Knowledge of AWS D17.1 desired.

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be able to work all shifts and available for overtime and weekends as needed.
Must be able to lift up to 25 lbs. unassisted and be agile enough to physically set-up and tear down components
Must be able to stand for extended periods &#8211; 8 hours min.
Must be able to stoop, bend, crawl, and being able to maneuver in tight spaces.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS: 

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR&#160;here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3081194603</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Friction Stir Weld Technician</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexfriction-stir-weld-technician2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.FRICTION STIR WELD TECHNICIANRESPONSIBILITIES:

Support hardware delivery projects for the development of structural components supporting the SpaceX family of products.
Support set up tooling and materials for friction stir welding projects under the direction of friction stir weld engineers and managers.
Assist with set up and operation of friction stir welding equipment.
Train in periodic maintenance on friction stir weld equipment.
Support friction stir weld production process under the direction of friction stir weld engineers and managers.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED required.
Experience using hand tools (grinders, torque wrenches, etc.).

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Associate degree in a technical field or Bachelor's degree in a STEM field
3+ years of experience in all or one of the following fields:

Welding
Structures assembly
Fabrication


Relevant friction stir welding experience.
Military experience.&#160;
3+ years of metal fabrication experience.
Prior experience working in a machine shop with CNC knowledge.&#160;
Experience working within a manufacturing or production environment
Basic knowledge of metallurgy of materials and joining processes.
Ability to perform basic shop mathematical skills such as fractional math and trigonometry.
Certifications from an accredited welding school.
Ability to meet deadlines and have a &#8220;whatever it takes&#8221; attitude to complete assignments.
Practical mechanical knowledge.

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be able to lift at least 25 lbs. unassisted.
Must be willing to travel. Up to 5% travel.
Must be able to climb ladders and work in tight spaces.
Must be willing to work all shifts, overtime, and weekends as needed.
Ability to pass Air Force background checks for Cape Canaveral and Vandenberg.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3679210381</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Integration Technician (Falcon 9)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexintegration-technician-falcon-92019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
INTEGRATION TECHNICIAN (FALCON 9)
The integration technician is responsible for the integration of the thrust structure comprising the engines, to the fuel stage. The task requires both avionics and mechanical integration skills along with pneumatic and avionics checkout activity. In short, it&#8217;s the final integration of the first stage of the Falcon 9 rocket, which was designed from the outset to deliver humans into space.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Stage, set up, assemble, test and install flight hardware.
Use precision calibrated tools &#8211; torque wrenches, micrometers and calipers.
Hands on operations with both large&#160;and small fragile assemblies.
Read and interpret blue prints.
Perform work according to procedures, specifications, and test instructions.
Use various mechanical tools without instruction.
Collaborate with production engineers to develop and document activities.
Ensure all production services are performed on time, safely and in a professional manner.
Perform other related duties, as assigned, for the purpose of ensuring an efficient and effective work environment.
Perform hydro and pneumatic testing.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED required.
5 years of propulsion or avionics hardware installation.

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Experience in the aerospace industry, aviation, military or other high-reliability operating environment preferred.
Experience with forklifts, cranes and heavy equipment is a plus.
Knowledge of pressure, temperature and flow measurement devices, mechanical and electrical systems, and propulsion engines.
Skill in operating and manipulating machinery and various hand and power tools requiring manual dexterity.
A demonstrated ability in reading/understanding technical drawings, manuals and reports.
Ability to use precision measuring instruments.
Ability to work effectively in a team environment.
Ability to rapidly change roles/responsibilities while working in a high-paced, challenging work environment.

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be able to lift at least 25 lbs unassisted.
Must be willing to travel up to 5%.
Must be able to climb ladders and work in tight spaces.&#160;
Ability to pass Air Force background checks for Cape Canaveral and Vandenberg.
Must be willing to work all shifts, overtime, and weekends as needed.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR&#160;here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3033480491</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Lead Orbital Tube Welder</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexlead-orbital-tube-welder2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
LEAD ORBITAL TUBE WELDER
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Assign and prioritize work based on production schedule.
Ensure all resources are assigned prior to official start of shift, with technicians allocated &amp; aligned per the skill matrix.
Review pass-down and update lead board with pertinent information.
Ensure product quality and conformance to specifications.
Ensuring all technicians are clocked into production work orders and working to the defined process time.
Schedule risk identification and mitigation activity.
Coordinate support organization efforts to minimize production interruptions.
Enforce area standards and run rules.
Personnel training and development.
Develop and implement efficiency improvement projects.
Root cause analysis and the implementation of corresponding corrective action plans.
Maintain area metrics and scheduling tools.
Maintain consumable supply inventory.
Check work after completion of each operation in&#160;job and/or completed job to ensure it is complete per drawing.
Coordinate support organization efforts to minimize production interruptions.
Work with your lead counterpart to tackle any schedule needs or shop improvement projects.
Communication briefing at start of shift with technicians.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED.
3 years' experience with TIG welding.
Experience welding stainless steel, inconel, and titanium.

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

SpaceX technician experience.
Proficient in blue print reading and lay out.
Knowledge and experience completing welds that pass visual before being X-rayed or dye penetrant inspected.
OTW certifications on required material types
Experience welding stainless steel, inconel, and titanium with wall thickness between .020" and .120".

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be open to work either 1st Shift&#160;(5:00am-3:30pm)&#160;or 2nd Shift (3:30pm-2:00am), overtime and weekends as needed.
Must be able&#160;to lift a minimum of 25 lbs. unassisted.
Must be able to stand for extended periods &#8211; 8 hours min.
Must be able to stoop, bend, crawl, and being able to maneuver in tight spaces.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1082509545</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Machine Maintenance Technician</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmachine-maintenance-technician2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
MACHINE MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Maintain and repair all assets to ensure their proper operating condition
Provide preventative and correct maintenance on various complex CNCs &#8211; 5 axis milling, mill turn applications, horizontal and vertical lathes
Troubleshoot and repair control &amp; electrical system failures involving &#8211; PLCs, HMIs, servomotors, servo amplifiers, Input/Output, field sensors, etc
Troubleshoot and repair various machine tool hydraulic &amp; pneumatic systems &#8211; actuators, valves, pumps, filters, etc
Troubleshoot, adjust and repair machine tool mechanical systems &#8211; ballscrews, linear rails, guideways etc
Perform regular CNC geometry assessments to validate machine accuracy
Drive forklifts and company vehicles
Perform other related duties, as assigned, for the purpose of ensuring an efficient and effective work environment

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
3+ years of maintenance technician experience
3+ years of experience with hydraulic, pneumatic, mechanical, and electrical repair
3+ years of experience with one or more of the following CNC control systems: Siemens 840D, Okuma, Fanuc, Heidenhain, Allen Bradley

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in a technical discipline
5+ years of experience as a maintenance technician or field service engineer
Experience installing and commissioning large CNC machines
Experience adjusting CNC geometry components including &#8211; squareness, backlash, linear compensation, servo timing
Experience using Renishaw calibration systems including XL-80 Laser Interferometer and Ballbar
Experience operating a forklift and other related inventory equipment
Ability to read and interpret electrical, hydraulic and pneumatic schematics and drawings
Ability to write detailed repair reports (advanced MS Office skills)
Ability to use power tools and hand tools as well as heavy equipment
Ability to maintain a safe and clean working environment while adhering to company policies, quality policies, and industry standards
Detail oriented, organized, and able to demonstrate a high sense of urgency
Analytic thinker that gets to the root of problems and comes up with permanent solutions to remedy issues
Self-motivated and able to work well with others

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>910413724</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Mechanisms Technician - Dragon Spacecraft</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmechanisms-technician-dragon-spacecraft2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.MECHANISMS TECHNICIAN&#160;&#8211; DRAGON SPACECRAFTAs a Mechanisms Technician on the Dragon spacecraft, you will be responsible for delivering an assembled Mechanisms to vehicle integration. The task requires both avionics and mechanical assembly skills along with pneumatic and avionics checkout activity. Your diligence and attention to detail will not only ensure mission success from launch to capsule splashdown, but will also ensure the safety of our astronauts.RESPONSIBILITIES:Stage, setup, assemble, install, and test flight hardware.Use precision calibrated tools &#8211; torque wrenches, micrometers and calipers.Hands on operations with both large and small fragile assemblies.Read and interpret technical drawings, and follow detailed work instructions.Perform high pressure pneumatic testing.Perform work according to procedures, specifications, and test instructions.Use various mechanical tools without instruction.Collaborate with production engineers and quality personal to develop and document activities.Ensure all production services are performed on time, safely and in a professional manner.Perform other related duties, as assigned, for the purpose of ensuring an efficient and effective work environment.BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:High school diploma or GED.Minimum of 3 years of at least one of the following trades:Mechanism assembly.Propulsion hardware assembly/test/installation.Avionics hardware assembly/test/installation.PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:Experience in the aerospace industry, aviation, military or other high-reliability operating environment.A&amp;P license strongly desired.Experience in fast-paced production environment with flight hardware.Knowledge of pressure, temperature and flow measurement devices, mechanical and electrical systems, and propulsion engines.Skill in operating and manipulating machinery and various hand and power tools requiring manual dexterity.5 years or more of aerospace mechanism assembly experience.A demonstrated ability in reading/understanding technical drawings, manuals and reports.Ability to use precision measuring instruments.Experience working in a cleanroom environment.Ability to work effectively in a team environment.Ability to rapidly change roles/responsibilities while working in a high-paced, challenging work environment.Ability to effectively communicate (verbal and written) with Engineering and Production.Proficient with computers and the ability to use MS Office.Experience with forklifts, cranes and heavy equipment.ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:Must be able to lift at least 25 lbs. unassisted.Must be able to climb ladders and be comfortable working in tight spaces.Must be willing to work all shifts, over time, and weekends as needed.ITAR REQUIREMENTS:To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR&#160;here.SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1645890343</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Orbital Tube Welder - Dragon Fluid Systems</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexorbital-tube-welder-dragon-fluid-systems2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.
ORBITAL TUBE WELDER &#8211; DRAGON FLUID SYSTEMS 
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Follow established procedures and work instructions to complete orbital tube welds on Dragon Fluids Systems.
Cut and prepare all tubing and fittings used in the welding operation.
Understand the quality requirements for orbital tube welds and be able to detect defects.
Final install welded assemblies which will include torqueing down assemblies and also applying adhesives to water seal mechanical connections.
Pneumatically test assemblies post welding.
Maintain a clean work area including the internals of the tubes and components being welded.

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED.
1 of either:

Certification from a formal orbital weld training program.
3 years of orbital welding experience.
Experience with TIG welding on aerospace materials such as Titanium, Stainless Steel, or Inconel.



PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

3 years&#8217; experience working in aerospace welding environment.
3 years&#8217; experience pneumatically testing welded assemblies or components.
Experience using a mass spectrometer.
Experience in a clean room environment.
Airframe and power plant license.

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be open to working all shift hours, overtime, and weekends as needed.
Must be able to lift a min. of 25 lbs. unassisted.
Must be able&#160;to stand for extended periods &#8211; 8 hours min.
Must be able to stoop, bend, crawl, and being able to maneuver in tight spaces.

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4274002231</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3728384726</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1856402174</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2114173528</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Satellite Solar Technician</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsatellite-solar-technician2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SATELLITE SOLAR TECHNICIAN
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Mechanical/electrical assembly of solar module and array components, and integration onto vehicle assembly
Operation of complex automated equipment, including troubleshooting and maintenance
Functional testing of built hardware, including setup, instrumentation, test execution, and tear down
Performing prototype hardware builds with minimal documentation and oversight, and working with engineering and production leadership to influence the designs for manufacturability and reliability
Managing schedule priorities and independently executing work to meet company deliverables

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Must have high school diploma or GED
Minimum of 3 years of experience using mechanical hand tools and/or automated machinery in a medium-to-high volume production environment

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Associate&#8217;s degree
Solar module production experience
Soldering experience
Composite experience (handling, layup, vacuum bagging, cure)
Experience maintaining and programming automated manufacturing equipment
Experience in fast-paced production environment with high quality requirements, e.g. military, aerospace, or medical industry
Able to adapt to constant changing work assignments and fast paced work environment
Excellent communication (written and verbal) and teamwork skills
Excellent concentration and attention to detail with outstanding work efficiency and accuracy

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be able to work all shifts and available for overtime and weekends as needed
Standing for long periods of time, climbing up and down ladders, bending, grasping, sitting, pulling, pushing, stooping, and stretching may be required to perform the functions of this position
Must be able to lift up to 25lbs. unassisted

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>WA</job_state>
    <job_city>Redmond</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1141809000</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>800842924</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1317860436</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Foundry Technician, Pattern and Shelling - Split/Night Shift</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexfoundry-technician-pattern-and-shelling-splitnight-shift2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
FOUNDRY TECHNICIAN, PATTERN AND SHELLING - SPLIT/NIGHT SHIFT
We are seeking an individual who is motivated, adaptable, inquisitive, has a high level of attention to detail, and is eager to learn new things. The Materials Technician will be responsible for learning the details of our processes as they evolve, and using that understanding to effectively and safely operate equipment and propose improvements that help SpaceX make world-changing launch vehicles and spacecraft. If this sounds exciting, we want to hear from you! &#160;
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Operate pattern making equipment and systems including plastic 3D printers, hand finishing, and wax dipping
Operate and maintain slurry systems for shell manufacturing including part loading, in-process inspection, and sampling
Take initiative in problem solving, cost reductions, and process improvement
Work with design engineers and tooling engineers to take products from design to production
Work with quality engineers to reduce defects and maintain high yield
Provide hands-on support to other foundry areas when developing prototype and production hardware
Provide hand finishing and assembly for printed components that meet critical dimensional tolerances
Take operational ownership of the equipment and processes for patterns and shells

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

2+ years of professional experience in a manufacturing or production environment
1+ years of hands-on experience with one or more of the following processes: 3D printing, gluing/assembling plastic parts, surface prep, inspecting parts, operator maintenance (PM&#8217;s) of sophisticated equipment, maintaining process fluids/chemicals, CNC equipment setups, designing/modifying fixtures, operating lab or manufacturing equipment, documenting improvements

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Demonstrated professional track record of creative problem solving, cost reductions, and process improvement
History of starting up new work centers and documenting info to establish solid processes
Experience taking products from design to production
Experience with 3D printers &#8211; operation and/or programming
Familiarity with HMI, PLC, or robot programming
Excellent hand work (sanding, cutting, assembly, etc.)
Comfortable with a mix of repetitive and new, one-off work
Experience with investment casting
Ability to effectively communicate with all levels of the organization
Excellent attention to detail

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

This position will require working from 1:30 PM to 12 AM

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR&#160;here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2788086450</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Manufacturing Engineer, Ceramics Processing</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmanufacturing-engineer-ceramics-processing2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.
MANUFACTURING ENGINEER, CERAMICS PROCESSING&#160;
As the Manufacturing Engineer you will be responsible for characterization and optimization of investment casting shells, ceramics processing, and finding, reviewing, and integrating new technologies for both development and production. You will also transition quickly and seamlessly between research and production environments.
RESPONSIBILITIES:&#160;

Provide materials and process support to all aspects of ceramic shells for investment casting
Manage the health, maintenance, and procedures associated with a series of high-solids slurries
Take initiative in problem solving, cost reductions, and process improvement
Work with design engineers and tooling engineers to take products from design to production
Use your strength in fundamental physical and materials science principles to drive production and design changes that result in superior products
Work with quality engineers to reduce defects and maintain high yield rates
Build data that shows relationships between processing operations and final quality
Provide hands-on support to manufacturing and test areas when developing prototypes and production hardware&#160;

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in ceramics engineering, materials science, metallurgy, chemical engineering, industrial engineering, or other technical discipline
3+ years of professional experience with characterization and optimization of ceramics or slurries

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Master&#8217;s degree in material science, materials engineering, or industrial engineering&#160;
Expert level first principle engineering knowledge of metals and other materials
Hands-on experience processing ceramics laboratory samples for characterization of powder, slurry, green, and fired ceramics
Demonstrated professional track record of process optimization and improvements in a manufacturing environment
Knowledge of physical and mechanical properties as well as evaluation methods (tensile strength, hardness, fatigue, fracture toughness, creep, stress rupture, SEM, non-destructive inspection, spectroscopy)
Experience with titanium, super alloy, and ferrous investment casting manufacturing processes including pattern making, die design, process control, product design standards, and quality systems
Strong knowledge of process and material-related defect formation and prevention
Experience with laboratory controls
Demonstrated research ability and strong project execution skills with a customer focus
SQL or other programming skills
Strong problem solving skills

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Travel as needed to suppliers and other SpaceX sites

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3298477031</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3508742769</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4115305572</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3112931762</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1677209776</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Security Protective Operations Center (SPOC) Operator</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsecurity-protective-operations-center-spoc-operator2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SECURITY PROTECTIVE OPERATIONS CENTER (SPOC) OPERATOR
SpaceX is looking for experienced operators for the SpaceX Security Protective Operations Center (SPOC), its global 24/7 monitoring and incident response coordination center. The ideal candidate will be a dedicated security professional with a demonstrated ability to work both independently and as a member of a team in a fast-paced high tech environment. As a SPOC Operator, you will coordinate day-to-day and incident response logistics, while providing support to security officers. SPOC Operators will also act as a point-of-contact for matters relating to each area facility and, as such, must coordinate closely with all operational, management, and administrative sections. Areas of responsibility include: event/incident monitoring, camera/security alarm monitoring, video review, dispatch, coordination of resources, and incident response management and communications.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Monitor, analyze, and report on daily global incidents that may impact SpaceX employees or offices, and escalate accordingly to security management, and subsequently to other key stake holders within the company
Maintain situational awareness company-wide via regular collaboration with all SpaceX sites and ensuring an understanding of the operations and facilities at all sites
Investigate incidents thoroughly, coordinate information gathering with involved Security personnel, and create accurate and timely incident reports
Make appropriate notifications and coordinate with onsite first responders, internal and external stakeholders, local law enforcement, and senior leadership during any incident or emergency.
Responsible for monitoring access control alarms, video surveillance equipment, fire alarm systems, and dispatching resources to investigate any anomalous alarms and activity with security personnel, uniformed security officers, and other departments as appropriate
Prioritize and process all incoming security reports and requests via radio, phone, and support ticket, and track all associated shift activity accordingly
Coordinate incident response logistics, provide direction and response instructions to uniformed security officers, and disseminate timely mass notifications when appropriate
Assist with video surveillance system reviews in support of investigations
Ensure thorough and current understanding of Security Protective Operations Center responsibilities, applicable SpaceX policies/procedures, security officer operations and all applicable security department initiatives
Perform additional duties as assigned by Security Leadership or SpaceX management

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

2+ years of experience in security operations in the professional, military, or law enforcement sectors

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Four-year college degree
Ability to communicate professionally and effectively with all levels of employees, guests, and executive leadership
Ability to assess and effectively escalate situations for proper resolution
Strong attention to detail
Work well in a fast-paced and multi-tasking, team focused environment
Learn, retain, and apply a variety of security related concepts, information and processes
Understanding of security systems (access control, video surveillance, and fire systems)
Effective Prioritization of tasks and responsibilities
Perform continuous follow-up on pending, open projects and tasks until completion
Strong analytical and critical thinking skills
Experience utilizing mass communication tools
Proficient in Microsoft Office suite

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be willing and able to work a flexible schedule (including quarterly rotations between days and nights) and cover occasional overtime as needed
Candidates will be subject to pre-employment screening (including background check, drug/alcohol test, psychology exam, polygraph, and sample writing test), and to random drug/alcohol testing throughout employment
If prior military, must be able to provide, upon job offer, a DD214 discharge document with discharge status indicated

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR here.&#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>954300761</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3834401935</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Propulsion Build Engineer (Raptor)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexpropulsion-build-engineer-raptor2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
PROPULSION BUILD ENGINEER (RAPTOR)
As a Raptor build engineer at SpaceX you will have the opportunity to apply your knowledge, experience, and creativity to develop hardware at the cutting edge of space technology. You will work on the engines that will ultimately extend humanity&#8217;s reach beyond the earth and moon. In this role, you will be the engineer responsible for the rapid manufacture and integration of parts, processes, and assemblies used on our next generation vehicles, providing input to both design/development and production.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Responsible for fabrication, assembly, and testing of Raptor propulsion parts, processes, assemblies, and/or systems
Work closely with design/development engineers and fabrications shops (internal and external) to get parts built and assembled
Develop manufacturing and test processes and procedures
Create and maintain a build schedule that lists all discrete fabrication and assembly tasks
Ensure that all parts are fabricated or purchased at the correct time to facilitate the build schedule
Own or participate in tool design and development
Resolve manufacturing discrepancies and interface with the cross functional teams
Manage the transition of parts from development to production
Document processes and drive continual improvements for future builds

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor's degree in an engineering discipline&#160;
At least 1 year of hands-on fabrication, assembly, and/or testing experience via internships, labs, outside the classroom extracurricular activities or professional industry experience

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Experience with NX or other solid modeling software
Experience with metallic or composite manufacturing techniques, processes, equipment, and other processes such as&#160;machining, welding, tube bending, structural assembly, etc.
Understanding of test methods/setups and data acquisition systems
Experience generating, reading, and interpreting engineering drawings
Experience with Design for Manufacture and Assembly (DFMA)
Experience in a team-oriented environment
Must be able to work well in an integrated collaborative team environment including daily interactions with technicians, engineers, and managers
Able to prioritize and execute tasks in a high-pressure environment
Self-motivated, well organized with keen attention to detail
Must have an ongoing drive for continuous improvement in all aspects of work

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Willing to work long hours and weekends as needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
&#160;
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4170685670</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3417294267</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4226200555</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3467103879</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>768812290</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Security Software Engineer</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsecurity-software-engineer2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SECURITY SOFTWARE ENGINEER
SpaceX is seeking technical, passionate engineers to build security solutions for some of the world&#8217;s most advanced technologies including: rockets, satellite constellations, ISP platforms, ground stations, and communication networks. We are looking for people who see the big picture, prioritize accordingly, and are comfortable with working at different levels of abstraction, and with a wide variety of technology.
Ideally, you will have notable skills in one or more of the following: red teaming, penetration testing, implementing advanced security technologies such as Secure Boot, or software engineering. Being flexible, communicating clearly, and establishing and maintaining productive working relationships with other engineering teams are paramount to success. If you love using your technical skills to solve challenging problems and want to make a great impact, then join SpaceX to be among the first to secure some of the world&#8217;s most innovative technologies.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Work with engineering teams to design security into systems and drive security reviews
Participate in Red Team exercises on the attack side
Catalyze security improvements that matter
Investigate technologies that could qualitatively improve security posture
Build prototypes and production systems
Develop and deploy tools to assist in modeling, analysis, detection, and prevention of security threats
Threat modeling, mitigation, validation, including software and hardware penetration testing
Stay current on developments affecting security and privacy policy

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s or advanced degree in an engineering or technical discipline; or 2+ years of software security experience without a degree
Experience designing and implementing security solutions for operating systems, distributed systems, and/or firmware/IoT devices
Experience in at least one of the following disciplines: red teaming, penetration testing, implementing advanced security technologies such as Secure Boot, or software engineering

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Fundamental understanding of network protocols; including the TCP/IP stack as well as UDP based protocols
Ability to analyze and design secure network architecture and communications protocols
Experience in navigating large, complex, interactive and/or distributed systems
Experience with fuzzing, buffer overflows, and other common exploits
Experience identifying and mitigating a range of security vulnerabilities
Experience with implementing or breaking Secure Boot
Experience with implementing or breaking secure communication systems
Experience with disassemblers and/or reverse engineering
Experience with hardware attacks
Experience in red teaming as an attacker
Penetration testing expertise
Security operations experience
Able to work on their own with little supervision, in a team, and with other teams and their processes
Able to establish and maintain good working relationships with colleagues and teams
Desire and ability to ramp up quickly on new technologies
Demonstrated skill in hardware and software security
Excellent communication skills both written and verbal
Able to deal with ambiguity

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>217562033</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Senior Full Stack Software Engineer</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsenior-full-stack-software-engineer2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today, SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.
Senior Full Stack Software Engineer&#160;
&#160;We are seeking a Senior Full Stack Software Engineer to build software used to design, develop, test, and launch rockets, spacecraft, and satellites. Our software engineers are involved in every facet of SpaceX by developing software solutions for things like tracking complex movement of parts, manufacturing integration assemblies, and even tracking telemetry of launch vehicles during a mission.
As a Full Stack Software Engineer, you will engage with other SpaceX engineers to discover the needs of the mission and write highly reliable software which turns the mission into reality. You will be responsible for the complete lifecycle of the software you create, including development, testing, and support.
You are the engineer that other engineers can count on; you are technical, you attack every problem with enthusiasm; you remove hurdles. You are a self-starter, team player, have the hunger to venture quickly into unknown areas and code and make the system work.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Build highly reliable software solutions for every part of SpaceX
Own all aspects of software engineering and product development
Act as a responsible engineer for various software products
Maintain highest standards of excellence, never settle for the status quo
Deep dive into your users&#8217; problems, find efficient solutions
Provide strong technical leadership, focus on continuous improvement

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in computer science, computer engineering, electrical engineering, math, or scientific discipline and 4+ years in software engineering, OR 6+ years in software engineering without a degree
2+ years of experience developing across a full-stack: web server, relational database, and client-side/front-end

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

5+ years of experience in web applications development
3+ years of experience as an architect - proven ability to design and implement robust and scalable systems with flexible and scalable UI that meets future needs
Expertise in C#., NET, SQL, HTML, CSS, AngularJS, TypeScript
Expertise in Python, PostgreSQL, Linux
Deep understanding of object oriented programming and design principles
Deep understanding of testing, continuous integration, build, deployment &amp; continuous monitoring
Experience scaling web applications and optimizing applications for performance
Solid understanding of UI/UX design to provide intuitive applications
Great creative and innovative problem-solving skills
Initiative and the ability to work independently and collaborate within a team

ITAR Requirements:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
&#160;
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3463954313</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Senior Software Engineer (Simulation Software)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsenior-software-engineer-simulation-software2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER (SIMULATION SOFTWARE)
As a software engineer on the Simulations team, you will design, develop, and test our in-house simulation software supporting all SpaceX flight systems. You will program the core simulation infrastructure and collaborate on the building of models of fluids, electronics, and multi-body physics systems. This is a high impact role where you will work across the engineering groups to build high fidelity simulations used to develop cutting-edge software and hardware. Our simulation software is critical to future mission successes including Starlink, Falcon Heavy and Starship. SpaceX is looking for smart, motivated software engineers who enjoy taking on complex challenges, work well in dynamic environments and care about software best practices.
Help us build world class software that is critical to SpaceX mission to Mars.
Responsibilities:

Develop high-fidelity simulation software for all vehicles
Improve reliability and performance of simulation software
Work with vehicle software and GNC teams to develop new features for testing in the simulation environment and improve user experiences
Provide strong technical leadership, focus on continuous improvement

Basic Qualifications:

Bachelor's degree in computer science, engineering, math, or science discipline and&#160;4+ years of experience in&#160;software development&#160;OR&#160;6+&#160;years of experience in&#160;software development
2+ years of experience in C/C++

Preferred Skills and Experience:

Strong software design and development skills
Thorough knowledge of physics and math
Strong skills in debugging, performance optimization and unit testing
Creative approach to problem solving
Ability to work effectively in a dynamic environment with changing needs and requirements
Ability to work independently and in a team, take initiative, and communicate effectively

Additional Requirements:

Willing to work extended hours and weekends when needed

ITAR Requirements:&#160;

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here.

&#160;
SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>555388526</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Senior Software Engineer (Vehicle)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsenior-software-engineer-vehicle2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER (VEHICLE SOFTWARE)
As an engineer on the vehicle software team, you will design, develop and test software that is used to control SpaceX flight systems. You will engage with other SpaceX software and hardware engineers&#160;to discover the needs of the mission and code highly reliable software that turns the mission into a reality. You will be responsible for the complete lifecycle of the software you create, from development to testing to operation during a mission.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Develop highly reliable autonomous software systems
Design and implement fault detection and mitigation in software
Develop prototypes to prove out key design concepts and quantify technical constraints
Own all aspects of software development, including design, testing, and mission integration
Provide strong technical leadership, focus on continuous improvement

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor's degree in computer science, engineering, math, or science discipline and&#160;4+ years of experience in&#160;software development&#160;OR&#160;6+&#160;years of experience in&#160;software development
2+ years of experience in C++

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Strong software design and development skills
Working knowledge of control theory
Experience designing fault tolerant software
Thorough knowledge of computer architecture and networks
Knowledge of physics, math, and electronics
Strong skills in debugging, performance optimization and unit testing
Creative approach to problem solving
Ability to work effectively in a dynamic environment with changing needs and requirements
Ability to work independently and in a team, take initiative, and communicate effectively

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Willing to work extended hours and weekends when needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1966109820</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Senior Technical Product Manager - Applications</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsenior-technical-product-manager-applications2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today, SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.
SENIOR TECHNICAL PRODUCT MANAGER - APPLICATIONS&#160;
We are seeking a hands on Product Manager to build software used to design, develop, test, and launch rockets, spacecraft, and satellites. Our Product Managers are involved in every facet of SpaceX by developing software solutions for things like tracking complex movement of parts, manufacturing integration assemblies, and even tracking telemetry of launch vehicles during a mission.
As a Product Manager, you will engage with business stakeholders and SpaceX engineers to discover the needs of the mission and write highly reliable software which turns the mission into reality.
You are the Product Manager that the business can count on; you code, you are technical, you attack every problem with enthusiasm; you remove hurdles. Not only do you enjoy tackling functional problems, you also enjoy diving into the code and implementing some requirements yourself. You are a self-starter, team player, have the hunger to venture quickly into unknown areas in code and roadmap.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Provide industry expertise in one of the following areas: Supply Chain, Warehouse Management, Manufacturing, Engineering, Quality/Reliability, Product Lifecycle Management, or high transaction systems such as eCommerce, Finance, and Business Operations Software
Analyze and break down problems and create potential solutions in order to evaluate outcome for the entire organization&#160;
Down-select and prioritize complex multi-layer cross-functional solutions to ensure the problem statements with the most impactful outcomes are selected for execution
Work with business stakeholders across SpaceX to obtain commitments on business process changes and organization readiness required to fully adopt the delivered solutions
Formulate product strategy, vision, and roadmaps to ensure we are on the quickest and best path for success
Build highly reliable software solutions for every part of SpaceX
Provide strong technical leadership, focus on continuous improvement
Work in the squads with engineers and designers to create most impactful and high quality solutions while eliminating unnecessary complexity and reducing operational burden
Analyze the outcome, usage, and adoption of delivered solutions to evaluate if the actual impact to the organization is in line with the planned expectations

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

5+ years of combined work experience as a developer, business systems analyst or product manager, with at least 2 of those years in Supply Chain, Warehouse Management, Manufacturing, Engineering, Quality/Reliability, Product Lifecycle Management, or high transaction systems such as eCommerce, Finance, and Business Operations Software
Hands on software development experience using front end and/or back end coding languages (C#, Python, CSS, HTML, Javascript, Angular, etc.)&#160;&#160;
Hands on experience with SQL

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in computer science, computer engineering, electrical engineering, math, or scientific discipline
10+ years of product management experience
5+ years of experience in web applications development
3+ years of experience as an architect - proven ability to design and implement robust and scalable systems with flexible and scalable UI that meets future needs
ERP and related systems development or implementation including Manufacturing Execution Systems (MES), Warehouse Management System (WMS), Quality Management and Execution Systems (QMS &amp; QES), Supply Chain and/or Financial Systems
Expertise in C#., NET, SQL, HTML, CSS, AngularJS, TypeScript
Expertise in Python, PostgreSQL, Linux
Deep understanding of object oriented programming and design principles
Deep understanding of testing, continuous integration, build, deployment &amp; continuous monitoring
Experience scaling web applications and optimizing applications for performance
Solid understanding of UI/UX design to provide intuitive applications
Great creative and innovative problem-solving skills
Initiative and the ability to work independently and collaborate within a team

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR&#160;HERE.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3420122881</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Software Engineer (Simulation Software)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsoftware-engineer-simulation-software2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SOFTWARE ENGINEER (SIMULATION SOFTWARE)
As a software engineer on the Simulations team, you will design, develop, and test our in-house simulation software supporting all SpaceX flight systems. You will program the core simulation infrastructure and collaborate on the building of models of fluids, electronics, and multi-body physics systems. This is a high impact role where you will work across the engineering groups to build high fidelity simulations used to develop cutting-edge software and hardware. Our simulation software is critical to future mission successes including Starlink, Falcon Heavy and Starship. SpaceX is looking for smart, motivated software engineers who enjoy taking on complex challenges, work well in dynamic environments and care about software best practices.
Help us build world class software that is critical to SpaceX' mission to Mars.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Develop high-fidelity simulation software for all vehicles
Improve reliability and performance of simulation software
Work with vehicle software and GNC teams to develop new features for testing in the simulation environment and improve user experiences
Provide strong technical leadership, focus on continuous improvement

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor's degree in computer science, engineering, math, or science discipline OR&#160;2+&#160;years of experience in&#160;software development
Programming experience in C++

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Strong software design and development skills
Thorough knowledge of physics and math
Strong skills in debugging, performance optimization and unit testing
Creative approach to problem solving
Ability to work effectively in a dynamic environment with changing needs and requirements
Ability to work independently and in a team, take initiative, and communicate effectively

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Willing to work extended hours and weekends when needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:&#160;

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
&#160;
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1495257696</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Software Engineer (Vehicle)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsoftware-engineer-vehicle2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SOFTWARE ENGINEER (VEHICLE SOFTWARE)
As an engineer on the vehicle software team, you will design, develop and test software that is used to control SpaceX flight systems. You will engage with other SpaceX software and hardware engineers&#160;to discover the needs of the mission and code highly reliable software that turns the mission into a reality. You will be responsible for the complete lifecycle of the software you create, from development to testing to operation during a mission.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Develop highly reliable autonomous software systems
Design and implement fault detection and mitigation in software
Develop prototypes to prove out key design concepts and quantify technical constraints
Own all aspects of software development, including design, testing, and mission integration
Provide strong technical leadership, focus on continuous improvement

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor's degree in computer science, engineering, math, or science discipline&#160;OR&#160;2+&#160;years of experience in&#160;software development.
Development experience in C/C++.

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Strong software design and development skills
Working knowledge of control theory
Experience designing fault tolerant software
Thorough knowledge of computer architecture and networks
Knowledge of physics, math, and electronics
Strong skills in debugging, performance optimization and unit testing
Creative approach to problem solving
Ability to work effectively in a dynamic environment with changing needs and requirements
Ability to work independently and in a team, take initiative, and communicate effectively

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Willing to work extended hours and weekends when needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2816012336</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Software Operations Engineer</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsoftware-operations-engineer2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SOFTWARE OPERATIONS ENGINEER&#160;
The&#160;Software Operations Engineer&#160;is a general purpose role that touches several technical and functional domains with the&#160;primary goal&#160;of ensuring entire application ecosystem is performing nominally.&#160;It supports a combination of homegrown and third party&#160;applications.&#160;Software Operations Engineer&#160;ensures that SpaceX&#8217;s systems are performing optimally and critical&#160;issue&#160;resolutions are appropriate to our 24/7 rocket manufacturing needs.&#160;&#160;Software Operations Engineer&#160;is both a customer and internal facing operational support role.&#160;This role handles a wide variety of issues including (but not limited to) application usability, technical investigations and solution implementation for bugs/incidents, production and test environment configurations, and report enhancements.&#160; Another critical part of the role is building automation, tools, and process improvements to reduce overall operational drag for the entire organization.&#160;
We hold ourselves highly accountable to keep our systems up and running smoothly and efficiently. This role is&#160;very&#160;challenging and demands passionate individuals who are comfortable with fast paced&#160;environments and driving solutions to unique problems. This is a great position to challenge yourself to build on your foundation of technical skills and functional domain expertise. You will constantly be challenged to work in a space you are not familiar with.&#160;&#160;If you are mission driven and are ready to work on mission critical systems,&#160;this is the team you are looking for.&#160;
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Implements small development changes to fix application, report, and infrastructure bugs and enhancements
Builds and maintains runbook documentation for regularly occurring issues
Provides end user support relating to usability questions,&#160;complex SQL changes, and root cause analysis on bugs
Provides off hours support for hot issues that must be resolved prior to next business day (must be willing to work on call to respond these critical issues during nights and weekends)
Provides internal support for&#160;infrastructure&#160;tasks such as deployment of labs, lab/deployment issue resolution, environment configurations, etc.&#160;
Coordinates and executes production software deployments
Pitches, drives, develops, and implements process and software improvements to improve overall operational efficiency
Implements automation or administrative tools to reduce drag on operations for repetitive tasks&#160;
Executes support and software administration for 3rd party software (primarily Teamcenter and NX)
Performs initial investigations for monitoring alerts and escalates to appropriate software teams when needed

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor's degree&#160;from an accredited university/college&#160;in&#160;Engineering, Physics, Mathematics, Computer Science, or Information Systems, or 1 year work experience technically supporting production software in an engineering/manufacturing organization
1 year&#160;SQL&#160;or similar DBMS coding language
Experience with front end and/or back end coding languages (C#, Python, CSS, HTML, Javascript, etc.)

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Experience supporting ERP systems
Experience in design/manufacturing environment
Ability to communicate with all levels of the organization
Excellence in problem solving and critical thinking skills
Project management skills to properly set, manage, and meet expectations to ensure quality of solution delivered
Familiar with&#160;Agile development practices
Ability to influence cross-functional teams without formal authority or structure
Strong presentation, verbal, and written communication skills
Experience maintaining software in a functional and technical capacity
Ability to write performant SQL queries and diagnose poor performing queries
High level knowledge of application architecture including concepts of authentication, web server, database servers, task servers, firewalls, monitoring systems, etc.
Experience using or administrating Teamcenter or NX
Experience with evaluating and comparing internal and external customer requests to ensure proper prioritization
Strong focus on continued education and cross-training
Experience&#160;using and administrating JIRA projects
Experience with Microsoft Office tools (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook)

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Willing to work extended hours and weekends when needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR&#160;here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
&#160;
&#160;
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>183478110</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1061724994</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Wireless Protocol Software Engineer</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexwireless-protocol-software-engineer2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
WIRELESS PROTOCOL SOFTWARE ENGINEER&#160;
RESPONSIBILITIES:&#160;

Design, code, maintain, test and document the link-layer protocol for the Satellite Communications Network
Collaborate with the MAC protocol design team for protocol development
Work with the PHY and Network teams to seamlessly integrate the link-layer within the Network stack
Integrate the link-layer with simulation infrastructure
Participate in architecture, design and code reviews and provide peer feedback

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:&#160;

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in computer science, computer engineering or electrical engineering OR 4 additional years of work experience
3+ years of experience in hands-on embedded C/C++ software development for communications protocols
1+ years of work experience in any of the L2, L3 protocol stack layers in broadband access technologies such as: WiFi, UMTS, LTE or satellite broadband
1+ years of experience with embedded Linux software development

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:&#160;

Master&#8217;s degree in computer science, computer engineering or electrical engineering
Experience in Multithread/Multicore programming
Experience with systems integration and testing methodologies
Experience with current software development processes and tools including Agile, TDD, BDD, CI, Git
Experience in Hardware/software integration like DMA, MMIO, etc.
Experience with JTAG, SWD debugging
Experience in modeling and validating MAC protocols using simulation tools like NS3, OPNET, etc.
Scripting ability with Python or similar
Skilled in troubleshooting and tuning of component hardware, software, networking and communications protocol problems
Understanding of network layer components such as IPv4, IPv6, Mobile IP, routing, forwarding, etc.
Proficiency with network monitoring protocols and tools such as SNMP, RMON, Wireshark, Ethereal
Experience with modern encryption and decryption methods and their implementation
Experience in development of very high performance SW with minimum delay and limited response time

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:&#160;

Must be willing to work extended hours and weekends as needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Palo Alto</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1260278694</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4128679359</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>23613376</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Buyer - Starlink Gateway Systems</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexbuyer-starlink-gateway-systems2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
Buyer - Starlink Gateway Systems
Responsibilities:

Overall responsibilities to support cross functional team of engineering, sourcing, and production of ground station antenna assemblies including but not limited to die castings, machined components, motors, radomes, RF, and electrical components
Determining best value suppliers, NPI sourcing plans, make vs. buy, should cost, buy complete strategies, and lead times, and drive design for manufacturability reviews with support from supplier quality and engineering
Lead supplier quality, development, and performance teams to execute the strategic procurement vision and visit supplier facilities and accurately assess technical capability, equipment, and capacity
Ensure continuity of supply through effective supplier management and lead supplier escalation meetings for parts shortages to develop recovery plan; proactively update SpaceX management and engineering teams on all critical supply issues
Drive demand, lead times, and track high risk materials and delivery performance, and also recover material shortages
Place purchase orders for material requirements planning (MRP) messages for production parts and resolve purchase order discrepancies and invoice issues
Manage materials across all nodes of our international, domestic, and in-house supply chains to include inventory management and safety stock planning as well as tracking of work in progress&#160;
Develop and maintain strong supplier relationships, analyze supplier spend, capacity, and lead times, and negotiate effectively to support cost, quality, and delivery goals and analyze procurement data and report metrics to improve supplier performance
Ensure compliance with all company policies and procedures and government regulations

Basic Qualifications:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in engineering, business, economics, supply chain, or similar technical discipline&#160;
3+ years of technical procurement experience

Preferred Skills and Experience:

Experience procuring mechanical, motors, thermoformed plastics, RF, harnessing, and electrical components
Knowledge of enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems such as WarpDrive applications, SAP, or Oracle
Experience reading datasheets, drawings, and blueprints
Understand process planning, materials and processes applications, quality procedures, Teamcenter 10, inventory management, and CapEx planning
Manufacturing or production line experience
Proven track record of leadership and team building skills
Exceptional analytical, problem solving, and organizational skills
Knowledge and skills in current technologies and applications, i.e. MS Office Suite, SQL, Access, etc.
Effective written, verbal and presentation communication skills
Ability to learn quickly and prioritize appropriately to meet customer and company needs
Excellent customer service skills
Detail oriented, self-motivated, and able to respond quickly to a fast-moving and ever-changing environment
Conducts all activities with the highest of integrity

Additional Requirements:

Ability to travel for short and extended trips as needed
Ability to work long hours and weekends as needed

ITAR Requirements:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1932914209</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4121872161</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>CMM Source Inspector - Portland, OR</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexcmm-source-inspector-portland-or2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.CMM SOURCE INSPECTOR - (Remote) - Portland, ORRESPONSIBILITIES:

Travel up to 95% of the time to perform visual and dimensional inspections on manufactured parts, assemblies, and/or sub-assemblies at supplier sites
Perform documentation review and verification of certifications, specifications, and conformance to design and specification requirements
Inspect flight hardware at the supplier according to engineering drawings, purchase order(s), industry standards, and SpaceX specifications
Perform the inspection on mechanical parts, components, assemblies and materials. May include but is not limited to purchased parts, in-process and final assemblies, and materials for workmanship and conformance to specifications / drawings
Ensure that all parts meet SpaceX specifications and standards or that any non-conformance is documented at the supplier
Support the development of inspection plans at suppliers
Support supplier corrective action process, including verifying corrective action implementation

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
Experience with receiving inspection, dimensional inspection, and coordinate measuring machine (CMM) inspection using PCDMIS programming language

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Experience reading and interpreting design drawings and computer-aided design (CAD) models
Strong Geometric Dimensioning &amp; Tolerancing (GD&amp;T) knowledge through experience and/or formal training
Demonstrated track record of excellent, high quality work&#160;
Experience with inspection equipment such as micrometer, calipers, profilometer, etc.
ISO9001/AS9100/9102 (First Article Inspection) experience
Strong computer skills, particularly with Microsoft Office products and CAD
Experience with Romer Arm
Precision mechanical inspection experience
Strong verbal and written communication skills
Self-motivated, efficient, trustworthy and able to work with limited supervision

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Ability to lift 30 lbs.
Lifting, standing, climbing, bending, grasping, sitting, pulling, pushing, stooping, stretching, and carrying are generally required to perform the functions of this position
Position may involve overtime, long hours and weekend work as needed. Occasional overnight stay may be required when traveling to suppliers
Frequent travel to suppliers around Portland, Oregon required. Valid driver&#8217;s license mandatory

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, applicant must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about ITAR&#160;here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3510243384</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2474484033</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3250557086</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1544171342</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Inventory Specialist (2nd Shift)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexinventory-specialist-2nd-shift2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
INVENTORY SPECIALIST (2nd Shift)
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Pick, lift, organize, and move standard hardware, raw material, purchased parts, machined details, and assemblies to support inventory control for the F9 rocket and Dragon spacecraft production
Assemble racks, look for parts, organize supplies, and any other tasks directed by inventory control lead and manager
Perform picking function to create necessary kits of parts, material, and hardware as required and assuring that all parts are accounted for and available in kits
Maintain strict material handling practices in accordance with good practice/procedures
Monitor shelf-life storage and maintain proper rotation of stock
Perform daily cycle counts
Effectively utilize ERP system

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
3 years of inventory control experience

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree
ERP system experience (SAP, Oracle, etc.)
Excellent computer skills including Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Outlook)
Experience and understanding of inventory and kitting processes
Capability to operate a forklift and other related inventory equipment
Experience within the aerospace, automotive, semiconductor, or electronic fields

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Ability to lift 25-30 lbs
Lifting, standing, climbing, bending, grasping, sitting, pulling, pushing, stooping, stretching, and carrying are generally required to perform the functions of this position
Ability to work all required shift hours, including overtime, and weekends, as needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here.

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2262330091</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Material Handler</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmaterial-handler2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>

SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.


MATERIAL HANDLER
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Support production/engineering with the movement of parts to support master schedule
Physically move and expedite materials when required in support of production/engineering and meet work order completion dates
Verify&#160;all materials are packaged and banded for transport, and assists with loading and unloading of trucks
Interface with receiving, quality control, purchasing and other related departments to resolve problems relative to receipt and distribution of material
Operate material handling equipment including but not limited to: forklifts, pallet jacks, and hand carts

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
Minimum 2 years of expediting/material handling experience within a manufacturing/production environment
Experience operating&#160;a forklift and/or material handling motorized vehicles and equipment
Experience with barcode scanning to document material movement

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

ERP experience
Experience working with aircraft or automotive parts and assemblies

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS: 

Ability to lift 30 lbs.
Lifting, standing, climbing, bending, grasping, sitting, pulling, pushing stooping, stretching and carrying are required to perform the functions of this position
Ability all required shift days and hours, and overtime, as necessary
Ability to work in an open aired environment, lacking temperature control

ITAR Requirements:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.



</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>FL</job_state>
    <job_city>Cape Canaveral</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1521227806</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Material Planner</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmaterial-planner2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
MATERIAL PLANNER
Material planning lies at the heart of SpaceX where our world-class rockets and spacecraft are built at an unprecedented rate. This is a high-profile, cross functional position that plays an integral role in enabling production flow and supporting launch manifest. Working in close coordination with Engineering and Manufacturing departments, material planners execute effective organization management and supply chain strategies to achieve production goals. With all integration taking place in-house, material planners are able to see their assemblies come to life every day!
RESPONSIBILITIES:
We are seeking planners with demonstrated experience in MRP (material requirements planning), supply chain practices, and project management. We need forward thinkers who can recover material shortages on purchased and fabricated parts by working cross-functionally to come up with creative solutions. One must also be able to analyze and interpret data and report to senior leadership to influence the organization. Help us build rockets reliably, cost-efficiently, and on-time!
BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in supply chain, business, engineering, or similar technical discipline
2+ years of professional experience in material planning, operations management, supply chain management, or master scheduling; or 2+ years of applicable internship experience in the same fields
Experience with MRP or ERP (enterprise resource planning) systems, and with managing bill of materials and work orders

PREFERRED SKILLS:

APICS (American Production and Inventory Control Society) certification, Six Sigma certification, or similar certifications
Proven ability to work in a fast-paced, cross functional environment, both independently and in a team
Demonstrated efficiency in time management, interpersonal communication, and organization
Strong skills in data analysis using Excel, SQL (Structured Query Language), and Tableau

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2206081289</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2176560007</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2672703775</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>4110333501</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>887227173</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Supply Chain Analyst (Source Inspection Program)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsupply-chain-analyst-source-inspection-program2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
SUPPLY CHAIN ANALYST (SOURCE INSPECTION) 
The SpaceX Supply Chain department is a critical player in our operations. To capitalize on our technical and market success, our team will execute large-scale projects that will define the bottom-line for the company. To be successful in this role, one must also be able to analyze and interpret data and report to senior leadership to influence the organization. Help us build rockets reliably, cost-efficiently, and on-time!
RESPONSIBILITIES: 

Scheduling source inspection events based on supplier requests and SpaceX production schedule
Assigning source inspectors to inspection events in a way that maximizes the support that can be provided
Learning, understanding and reinforcing SpaceX policies and procedures
Integrates with cross-functional partners to understand current processes and identify gaps
Creates reports, tools, and standardized metrics for operational measurements and improvements
Compile regular supply chain reports, review and analyze for solutions to unsatisfactory trends
Support department continuous improvement projects such as new process rollouts, standardization, and furnishing information as directed

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor&#8217;s degree in business, supply chain, management information systems, computer information systems, computer science, engineering, or a similar technical discipline
1+ year of experience in supply chain reporting and analytics

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Experience with structured query language (SQL) and creating dashboards
Effective project management skills
Understanding of database structures, SQL query, and Tableau
Exposure to enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems
Experience in a manufacturing or distribution environment
Experience with process mapping and process improvement
Ability to identify and maintain priorities for tasks and projects
Ability to work in a fast-paced, cross-functional environment, both independently and with a team
Ability to develop and maintain strong relationships across disciplines
Comfortable with Microsoft Suite

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Position may involve long hours and weekend work as needed

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1816018597</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Supply Chain Reliability Engineer - Surveillance</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexsupply-chain-reliability-engineer-surveillance2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of enabling human life on Mars.
SUPPLY CHAIN RELIABILITY ENGINEER - SURVEILLANCE
The supply chain team is responsible for the sourcing, planning, procurement, warehousing, and transportation of all raw materials and components needed to build our revolutionary spacecraft and launch vehicles. Our mission is to get the right part in the right place at the right time, every time.
The supply chain reliability engineering team is chartered with global quality surveillance of the supply base, reducing supply chain risk through external evaluations and internal risk reviews, leading failure investigations and proactively driving source qualification activities.
As a supply chain reliability engineer, you manage and lead cross functional risk activities to meet technical, production, and regulatory requirements at the point of qualification and throughout the supplier&#8217;s lifecycle. You would perform source qualification events and approve new capabilities at suppliers. You would be responsible for monitoring for known and unknown supplier flight risk and driving failure investigations to resolve issues immediately and effectively. As supplier surveillance activities deal with suppliers that support all areas of SpaceX, you would build an extensive network within materials and processing, build reliability, production, supply chain management, and a deep understanding of SpaceX systems and processes. This experience would enable you to become a critical voice in the development of group and company strategy.
To be successful, you will need:

A deep technical and practical knowledge of manufacturing processes and standards
The capability to project manage and drive accountability within cross functional teams, succinctly communicate status and needed action, often urgently, to all levels of the organization
A willingness to roll up your sleeves and step into chaotic situations, using technical knowledge and quality background to understand the current state and most optimal path forward
The ability to analyze for and identify suboptimal supplier and internal system process gaps and drive improvement through data driven decisions
The ability to conduct formal and informal supplier evaluations, corrective actions, and process reviews
An ability to acquire new technical knowledge, particularly around how purchased components and assemblies integrate into the rocket and spacecraft

RESPONSIBILITIES:

Proactively perform independent technical field qualification and verification of supplier capabilities and ongoing reliability. Execute corrective actions as a result of audit
Monitor and assess supplier capabilities for unknown flight risk and work to resolve issues. Assess changes in supplier processes and asses for cross-functional impacts. Run risk review activities, including performing and organizing data reviews and executing mitigation plans
Lead cross functional supplier quality investigations (probationary reviews). Coordinate failure resolution and follow-up actions to avoid further mishaps. Author and edit quality alerts for regulatory and customer
Work directly with engineering and M&amp;P teams to develop and install new process qualification requirements
Review acceptance and qualification of new capabilities at suppliers. Ensure reliability and maintainability of modified capabilities through a risk-based re-qualification program
Perform early supplier failure detection and warning analysis
Maintain holistic supply chain capabilities knowledge and work with cross-functional teams to drive improved verification and changes for improved reliability

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelors degree in an engineering field
3+ years of experience in a manufacturing environment

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Masters degree in an engineering discipline
Knowledge and mastery of principles of chemistry, engineering, fluid dynamics and mechanics of materials
Ability to quickly grasp knowledge of a diverse range of supplier capabilities
Practical experience in requirement and specification development
Capable of seeking and solving complex problem and organizing it in a manner that helps decision-making
Demonstrated experience in leading or working on a multi-disciplinary engineering problem
Experience with quality systems (ISO 9000/AS9100/NADCAP/TS)

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Position may involve long hours and weekend work as needed
Ability to travel - up to 60-75% work week travel is expected

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
&#160;
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Hawthorne</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2917328852</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Maintenance Technician - Temporary</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexmaintenance-technician-temporary2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN - TEMPORARY
Rocket Development Facility Maintenance Technicians work in a fast paced testing environment, where the extraordinary becomes the everyday. The Maintenance Technicians will be involved in all aspects component and systems maintenance. They will utilize all tools at their disposal to ensure reliability of test stands on development and production test stands. This will involve corrective, preventive and predictive maintenance techniques as well as operational and design feedback for maintaining and improving all systems at the Rocket Development Facility.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Maintain and repair ground support equipment on test stands and facilities systems including pumps, tanks, valves, plumbing and instrumentation
Troubleshoot, diagnose and repair hardware associated with: high pressure gas; hydraulic; cryogenic systems and components and associated instrumentation
Maintain structural systems and components such as: rollers; bearings; rams etc.
Collaborate with design and test engineers to maintain systems in peak operating condition
Follow all regulations and appropriate SpaceX procedures including quality policies, safety policies, OSHA, EPA, NIOSH, NFPA, ASME, NEC and other standards
Develop novel methods to streamline processes site-wide to increase reliability of internal processes

POSITION DETAILS:
This is a temporary position with SpaceX, for the length of time as stated, and is subject to change with minimal notice as business needs dictate.

LENGTH OF POSITION: 6 months
LOCATION: McGregor, TX
SHIFT: 1st, must be available for overtime and weekends as the schedule varies depending on site operational needs; flexibility is required

&#160;BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED
2+ years of experience as a maintenance technician
4+ years of experience with hydraulics, cryogenic, pneumatic, mechanical or electrical/data systems

PREFERRED SKILLS &amp; EXPERIENCE:

Associate degree in a technical field
Experience with CMMS systems such as Maximo, SAP, etc.
Knowledge in the following areas desired: vacuum systems; bore scope inspections/operation; tubing and pipe fittings/joints; wide variety of mechanical fasteners; HVAC; rotating machinery (pumps, air compressors, etc.)
Formalized training/experience in the following fields: power plant, oil industry, aerospace, automotive or electronic (semi-conductor) fields
Knowledge of high pressure gas, hydraulic, cryogenic, flammable, hypergolic, pyrophoric systems
Experience with carpentry, painting, heavy equipment, grounds/building/industrial maintenance
Experience in maintenance, calibration, troubleshooting instrumentation, process controls and data and control systems
Programmable Logic Controller (PLC) programming and troubleshooting experience
Basic understanding of the theory of operation for the following instrumentation: pressure transducers, thermocouples (K&amp;E), RTDs, load cells, flowmeters, and others
Operational knowledge of an oscilloscope &amp; multi-meter, soldering wires &amp; connectors, operation of various crimping tools, wire stripping, ohm&#8217;s law, continuity testing, pinning out a military type connector, routing &amp; tie wrapping cables, drilling &amp; tapping holes, and building junction boxes

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Must be detail oriented, organized, and demonstrate a high sense of urgency
Ability to lift heavy objects (up to 30lbs unassisted)
Lifting, standing, climbing, bending, grasping, sitting, pulling, pushing, stooping, stretching, and carrying are generally required to perform the functions of this position
Must be available for overtime and weekends as the schedule varies depending on site operational needs; flexibility required
Work routinely performed in extreme outdoor environments &#8211; heat, cold, rain.
Ability to write detailed repair reports
Able to use power tools, hand tools and power equipment
Ability to maintain a safe and clean working environment

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR&#160;here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
&#160;
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>TX</job_state>
    <job_city>McGregor</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2398317760</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1951459238</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>728094913</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Build Engineer (Starship)</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexbuild-engineer-starship2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
BUILD ENGINEER (STARSHIP)
The Build Engineer role is responsible for design for manufacturability concepts through integration and testing of the full vehicle, and everything in between. Build Engineers will be highly engaged on the primary and secondary structures of the vehicle, including designing tooling (assembly aide, welding, part fixturing, etc.) and processes (welding, large part movement, large structure integration) to rapidly build early versions of the Starship and Super Heavy vehicles. Further along in the build, this role will be responsible for items such as integration operations sequencing, and working with technicians on installing flight-critical hardware on the vehicle. Throughout the build, engineers will be responsible for documenting processes, and driving continual improvement to them for future builds. Furthermore, Build Engineers will be expected to sometimes act as de-facto supervisors and advisors to production technicians, welders, and other skilled labor partners. Build Engineers will spend time both in the office and on-site (local production floor and remote build sites) to execute on the mission to build an orbital-capable Starship and Super Heavy faster than anyone though possible.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Work closely with vehicle analysts and design team to ensure solutions meet the requirements for vehicle design as well as the manufacturing processes
Develop production procedures/processes and manage the transition of parts and assemblies from development to high rate production
Coordinate and execute development, qualification, and acceptance testing of systems and tooling needed to meet hardware deadlines
Execute design for manufacturability changes to enhance production efficiency
Create original CAD models and prints for flight and/or tooling components
Lead the on-site design engineering contact for the efficient build of parts and assemblies
Create and maintain build schedules
Resolve and analyze manufacturing discrepancies, while interfacing with the quality team (resolving issues for design, fabrication and assembly)
Participate in design reviews internally and with suppliers and customers
Partner with engineering &amp; production teams to generate ideas, designs, and improvements for current and next-generation vehicles&#160;
Source, retain and advise new and experienced vendors from a technical perspective

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor's or advanced degree in aerospace engineering, manufacturing engineering, materials engineering, mechanical engineering or engineering physics
Hands-on project experience with complex mechanical systems, preferably as a team or sub-team lead
2+ years of manufacturing design experience (student project team and internship experience counts)

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

2+ years of professional experience in the field of aerospace/mechanical engineering
2+ years of experience with GD&amp;T concepts
Previous experience working on SpaceX vehicles or builds&#160;
Experience with fluid dynamics, finite element, or related computer-based modeling
Experience with large steel structure construction (civil, naval, or mechanical)
Experience leading operation-critical part mechanical design, including basic structures calculations and design considerations
Experience with finite element analysis (FEA) software packages
Process development, facility and line layouts, error-proofing
Experience with Unigraphics NX and Teamcenter CAD and PLM systems
Detailed knowledge of Siemens NC or similar CAD and PLM packages
Prior experience with developing, maintaining and improving welding processes
Strong interpersonal and organizational skills

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Flight hardware typically is built in tight quarters and physical dexterity is required
Ability to perform job duties that require standing, kneeling, crouching, twisting upper body, working in cramped positions in small openings and climbing hand over hand
Typically exposed to work in extreme outdoor environments &#8211; heat, cold, rain
Work performed in an environment requiring exposure to fumes, odors, and noise
Schedule varies depending on site operational needs; flexibility required
Flexibility to travel to remote build sites

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>TX</job_state>
    <job_city>Brownsville</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2520609533</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3644009357</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2772452065</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1504425798</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>2775904581</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1484064581</id>
    <employer_id>1</employer_id>
    <company_name>SpaceX</company_name>
    <company_url>www.spacex.com</company_url>
    <company_email>elon@spacex.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Vehicle Integration Technician - Temporary</job_title>
    <job_slug>spacexvehicle-integration-technician-temporary2019-05-31</job_slug>
    <job_description>
SpaceX was founded under the belief that a future where humanity is out exploring the stars is fundamentally more exciting than one where we are not. Today SpaceX is actively developing the technologies to make this possible, with the ultimate goal of&#160;enabling human life on Mars.
VEHICLE INTEGRATION TECHNICIAN (STARSHIP) - TEMPORARY
The Vehicle Integration Technician is responsible for the integration of all secondary structure, avionics, and stage propulsion components and systems to the vehicle&#8217;s primary structure. The task requires both avionics and mechanical integration skills along with pneumatic and avionics checkout activity.
RESPONSIBILITIES:

Stage, set up, assemble, test and install flight hardware
Use precision calibrated tools
Hands on operations with both large&#160;and small fragile assemblies
Heavy rigging for large assemblies
Operation of personnel platforms (boom lifts, scissor lifts, etc.)
Read and interpret engineering drawings and work instructions
Perform work according to procedures, specifications, and test instructions
Use various mechanical tools without prior instruction
Collaborate with production engineers to develop and document integration processes
Ensure all production services are performed on time, safely and in a professional manner
Perform fluids and pneumatic testing
Ability to work effectively in a team environment

POSITION DETAILS:
This is a temporary position with SpaceX, for the length of time as stated, and is subject to change with minimal notice as business needs dictate.

LENGTH OF POSITION: 12 months; through May 2020
LOCATION: Cape Canaveral, FL
SHIFT: 1st shift or 2nd shift

BASIC QUALIFICATIONS:

High school diploma or GED&#160;
3+ years of&#160; experience with propulsion or avionics hardware installation

PREFERRED SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE:

Experience in the aerospace industry, aviation, military or other high-reliability operating environment&#160;
Experience with forklifts, cranes and heavy transport equipment
Knowledge of pressure, temperature and flow measurement devices, mechanical and electrical systems, and propulsion engines
Skill in operating and manipulating machinery and various hand and power tools requiring manual dexterity
Ability to use precision measuring instruments
Ability to rapidly change roles/responsibilities while working in a high-paced, challenging work environment
FAA Airframe and PowerPlant license
Proficient with computers and the ability to use MS Office

ADDITIONAL REQUIREMENTS:

Willing to travel up to 25%. Position is based in Cape Canaveral, FL, however work at other SpaceX facilities for extended periods for similar work may be required
Ability to climb ladders and work in confined spaces
Ability to pass Air Force background check for Cape Canaveral
Willing to work all shifts, overtime, and weekends as needed
Ability to lift at least 25 lbs unassisted

ITAR REQUIREMENTS:

To conform to U.S. Government space technology export regulations, including the International Traffic in Arms Regulations (ITAR) you must be a U.S. citizen, lawful permanent resident of the U.S., protected individual as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3), or eligible to obtain the required authorizations from the U.S. Department of State. Learn more about the ITAR&#160;here. &#160;

SpaceX is an Equal Opportunity Employer; employment with SpaceX is governed on the basis of merit, competence and qualifications and will not be influenced in any manner by race, color, religion, gender, national origin/ethnicity, veteran status, disability status, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, mental or physical disability or any other legally protected status.
Applicants wishing to view a copy of SpaceX&#8217;s Affirmative Action Plan for veterans and individuals with disabilities, or applicants requiring reasonable accommodation to the application/interview process should notify the Human Resources Department at (310) 363-6000.
</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>FL</job_state>
    <job_city>Cape Canaveral</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-31</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3649177152</id>
    <job_expires_at>2019-06-03</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>1</is_approved>
    </job>
  </jobs>
</wpjb>
