<wpjb>
  <jobs>
    <job>
      <id>2504357445</id>
    <employer_id>3</employer_id>
    <company_name>XPrize</company_name>
    <company_url>https://www.xprize.org/home</company_url>
    <company_email>test@blueorigin.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Senior Research Analyst</job_title>
    <job_slug>xprizesenior-research-analyst2019-05-23</job_slug>
    <job_description>We are looking for a passionate senior analyst to conduct research on political, social, economic, technological and environmental challenges and trends; and analyze policies, innovation programs, technological developments, and related issues. As a senior analyst you should be able to quickly and effectively study various domains, global issues (e.g. space, environment, education, energy, and human health and longevity), and their related challenges. The candidate will collect and analyze data, support the development and execution of an on-line community of experts and practitioners, as well as conduct interviews with subject matter experts in order to gather key insights and feedback related to the research. The candidate will determine the most appropriate research methodology required for specific tasks, and will be responsible for scoping the project, including developing the full research plan.&#160;</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Culver City</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-23</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-05-26</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3790762986</id>
    <employer_id>3</employer_id>
    <company_name>XPrize</company_name>
    <company_url>https://www.xprize.org/home</company_url>
    <company_email>test@blueorigin.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Director, Software Development</job_title>
    <job_slug>xprizedirector-software-development2019-05-23</job_slug>
    <job_description>&#160;-PETER DIAMANDIS Our Values:</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Culver City</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-23</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-05-26</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>187043526</id>
    <employer_id>3</employer_id>
    <company_name>XPrize</company_name>
    <company_url>https://www.xprize.org/home</company_url>
    <company_email>test@blueorigin.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Full Stack Developer</job_title>
    <job_slug>xprizefull-stack-developer2019-05-23</job_slug>
    <job_description>&#160;-PETER DIAMANDIS Our Values:</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Culver City</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-23</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-05-26</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>3520402574</id>
    <employer_id>3</employer_id>
    <company_name>XPrize</company_name>
    <company_url>https://www.xprize.org/home</company_url>
    <company_email>test@blueorigin.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Project Manager, Prize Operations</job_title>
    <job_slug>xprizeproject-manager-prize-operations2019-05-23</job_slug>
    <job_description>XPRIZE CULTURE The fast-pace environment and energy at XPRIZE HQ rivals Silicon Valley vibrant tech startups.&#160; Our people are passionate about the impact we&#8217;re making on this world, and are upbeat, enjoy working together and are 100% committed to our movement.</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Culver City</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-23</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-05-26</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>594163367</id>
    <employer_id>3</employer_id>
    <company_name>XPrize</company_name>
    <company_url>https://www.xprize.org/home</company_url>
    <company_email>test@blueorigin.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Director Organizational Development &amp; Talent Strategy</job_title>
    <job_slug>xprizedirector-organizational-development-talent-strategy2019-05-23</job_slug>
    <job_description>The Organizational Development &amp; Talent Strategy Director role has the influence to dramatically improve the Foundation&#8217;s well-being of their employees as well as the ability to impact the employee experience. The role will provide leadership and vision to performance management, talent management in the areas of engagement and culture, and learning and development. The overall purpose of the role is to help people function better within the organization.&#160; The key will be to align our talent strategy with company goals and direct the successful implementation of initiatives necessary to drive long-term high performance. The role will act as a brand ambassador and weave in the brand experience through every expression of the OD and talent strategy and process.&#160; Essential Functions</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Culver City</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-23</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-05-26</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  <job>
      <id>1838366571</id>
    <employer_id>3</employer_id>
    <company_name>XPrize</company_name>
    <company_url>https://www.xprize.org/home</company_url>
    <company_email>test@blueorigin.com</company_email>
    <job_title>Senior Director, Individual Giving</job_title>
    <job_slug>xprizesenior-director-individual-giving2019-05-23</job_slug>
    <job_description>The Senior Director of Individual Giving for the XPRIZE Foundation is a new and exciting opportunity for a seasoned fundraiser to create, implement, and manage a robust Individual Giving program to support ongoing operations for the Foundation. The successful candidate will be a metrics-driven major gift fundraiser, experienced in building new fundraising programming and systems, proven in working with volunteer leaders and high-level prospects, able to lead and mentor colleagues, and a professional who thrives in a dynamic, entrepreneurial culture. Reporting to the Vice President of Development, the Senior Director of Individual Giving supervises the Individual Giving Manager and Individual Giving Associate. The role will involve oversight of a new Individual Giving program, which will include creating giving opportunities at all levels of support, engagement strategies throughout the giving spectrum, and a communication strategy to reach new and existing donors. The individual in the position will also develop and maintain a portfolio of high-level prospects.</job_description>
    <job_country>840</job_country>
    <job_state>CA</job_state>
    <job_city>Culver City</job_city>
    <job_created_at>2019-05-23</job_created_at>
    <job_expires_at>2019-05-26</job_expires_at>
    <is_active>1</is_active>
    <is_approved>0</is_approved>
    <is_filled>0</is_filled>
    <is_featured>0</is_featured>
    </job>
  </jobs>
</wpjb>
